<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<root>
  <step index ="1">
    <node idx ="0">
      <text></text>
      <!--just for timer-->
    </node>

    <node idx ="1">
      <text>Hello manager. Welcome to Lobotomy Corporation. Starting today you are responsible for managing the abnormalities we have and ensuring that we meet the daily energy quota.</text>
      <!-- 화살표, 하이라이트도 여기에 추가 -->
    </node>

    <node idx ="2">
      <text>You can move the camera around with the W, A, S, and D keys on your keyboard. You can also press and hold the secondary mouse button (RMB) and drag the mouse.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="3">
      <text>You can zoom the screen in and out with the F and G keys on your keyboard. The scroll wheel on the mouse can also be used.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="4">
      <text>Let's try a simple maneuver. When you hover your mouse over an employee, some information about them will be show on the top right corner. Please try selecting an employee by pressing the primary mouse button (LMB).</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="5">
      <text>Well done. The information displayed in the panel on the right is related to the selected employee. Some of this information is important, such as their state and E.G.O equipment. Please look article in the manual titled &lt;Employees&gt; for more details about what the information means.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="6">
      <text>The bar at the top left of the screen displays the amount of energy you need to collect to end the day. The top right corner lists what missions you are able to clear today.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="7">
      <text>Energy is produced when a product called Positive Enkephalin (PE, a green box) is released by an abnormality. This can occur while it is being worked on. Please click on the containment unit that holds an abnormality with the primary mouse button (LMB).</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="8">
      <text>Since you have yet to learn (unlock) any information about this abnormality, you have no way of knowing how it will respond to the 4 different works. In order to learn this information, an employee has to perform a work with it. For now, please select the first type of work availible, Instinct work.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="9">
      <text>Instinct work satisfies an abnormality's primal and physiological desires. When an employee conducts Instinct work, their Fortitude will increase at the end of the day. Increasing Fortitude raises their Health Points (HP).</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="10">
      <text>Every work you can request your employees to perform on abnormalities will have different results. These results differ for each abnormality. The success rate for type of work also varies per abnormality.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="11">
      <text>A fragile mind can be quite strained when meeting an abnormality. If your employee is not mentally ready, it may make the abnormality seem more frightening or disturbing to them. As such, they may have a serious reaction encountering it, which will lower their Sanity Points (SP).</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="12">
      <text>Abnormalities release Enkephalin when employees work with them. We collect this into boxes. Depending on how the employee performs the work, the abnormality will respond either Positively or Negatively. When it reacts positively, it will release Positive Enkephalin, which produces a green PE-Box.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="13">
      <text>However, if the abnormality reacts negatively, it will release Negative Enkephalin instead, and damage the employee. Please keep in mind that when an employee's Health or Sanity drops completely, the work is forcefully ended.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="14">
      <text>An abnormality's mood might change depending on the outcome of the work done with it. This outcome can be predicted based on the amount of PE-Boxes we obtained thanks to the work. An abnormality has generally three ways of responding: Good, Neutral and Bad. Depending on the outcome, it may use a special ability or try to escape.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="15">
      <text>When the work is finished, the energy and PE-Boxes that were generated are collected. PE-Boxes are stored and shown in the abnormality's PE-Box counter. Each abnormality produces a set of PE-Boxes unique to them. These can be used to unlock more of an abnormality's information which in turn increases the observation level, or to extract E.G.O Equipment from it.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="16">
      <text>After a work has been performed with an abnormality, you cannot work again with it for a short period of time. Until you can work with it again, you can send your employees to work with other abnormalities or let them heal up.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="17">
      <text>When the regenerator gauge fills up completely, employees in the main room will be healed. This will restore both their Health (HP) and Sanity (SP).</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="18">
      <text>Let's try ordering an employee to go work using a different method. First, click on the employee using the primary mouse button (LMB).</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="19">
      <text>Now use the secondary mouse button (RMB) to click on the abnormality containment unit. (Please be aware you can accidentally deselect the employee)</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="20">
      <text>We still don't know much about this abnormality, so order the employee to perform Insight work with it.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="21">
      <text>Insight work is conducted to improve the environment in which the abnormality resides. When an employee conducts Insight work, their Prudence will increase at the end of the day. Increasing Prudence raises their Sanity Points (SP).</text>
    </node>
  <!-- Add more corrections here -->
    <node idx ="22">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="23">
      <text>You seem to have collected enough of this abnormality's PE-Boxes. It's time to learn about observation. Please press the label bar (nameplate) displayed at the top of the containment unit. At the moment it displays the subject number instead of the name. After unlocking the abnormality's basic information, the name will be displayed here instead.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="24">
      <text>This displays the information we currently have on the abnormality. As you can see, we have little knowledge about it, as most of it is locked away.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="25">
      <text>You need to spend some of the unique PE-Boxes we collected from the abnormality in order to gain detailed information. Please try to unlock some information about the abnormality.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="26">
      <text>Details about managing the abnormality are displayed here. If the abnormality doesn't like something, the Qliphoth Counter can decrease and cause problems for energy production, so make sure you unlock and read these thoroughly. Please try to unlock it now.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="27">
      <text>How abnormalities react to different types of work is displayed here. The more it likes a type of work, the higher the success rate. The number on the left indicates the level of employee skill needed for the associated success rate. Please unlock all of its work preferences now.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="28">
      <text>Let's proceed. This area shows the abnormality's Qliphoth Counter maximum. It also shows whether an abnormality will escape when the Qliphoth Counter reaches 0 as well as its resistance to different types of damage after it has escaped, which is useful to know for abnormality suppression. Please unlock its escape information now.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="29">
      <text>You are now finished observing this abnormality. As you unlock more information the abnormality observation level will increase and give benefits when working with the abnormality, such as an increased work speed or success rate.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="30">
      <text>After increasing the observation level past a certain point, you can extract E.G.O Equipment from the abnormality at the cost of PE-Boxes. E.G.O Weapons are powerful tools that can help with suppressing and studying abnormalities. Please extract an E.G.O Weapon.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="31">
      <text>E.G.O Suits offer increased resistance to certain types of damage. Some damage types may hit harder than others depending on what E.G.O Suit an employee wears. Please extract an E.G.O Suit.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="32">
      <text>Well done. You can see the E.G.O Gift the abnormality has a chance to give an employee here. If this area is unlocked, employees have a chance to receive the E.G.O Gift after completing work with the abnormality. Usually the chance of this is slim.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="33">
      <text>Lastly, let's check the abnormality's observation records. Please click on Abnormality Story.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="34">
      <text>You can see the abnormality's obversation records here. Entries are added as the observation level increases. Looks like we've now reviewed everything, so let's close this information window. Please click on Leave.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="35">
      <text>Now that you've unlocked the abnormality's basic information, some is shown on top of the containment unit. Furthermore, since we unlocked its work preferences, we know it prefers attachment work. Let's try ordering an employee to perform attachment work on it. Click on the abnormality's containment unit.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="36">
      <text>Some basic information is shown here as well, which can be useful. Please order an employee to do attachment work.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="37">
      <text>Since you unlocked the work preference details for attachment work, the success rate and job length are displayed for the employee. You can also see further details of the employee when you hover your mouse over them which can help you to make better decisions when giving orders. Please select an employee to do the work.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="38">
      <text>Let me warn you about one more thing. When your employees enter a containment unit to work with an abnormality, the Qliphoth Meltdown guage is filled up by one block.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="39">
      <text>When the gauge is filled up completely, a Qliphoth Meltdown will occur. The number next to the guage shows how many containment units will be affected. Affected containment units will show a Meltdown Alert just above.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="40">
      <text>When a Qliphoth Meltdown happens, the containment unit displays a timer bar next to the alert. Normally this slowly drops, but the timer is paused when an employee works on an abnormality when the Meltdown starts, and does not count down until work is finished.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="41">
      <text>The meltdown can be prevented by working with the abnormalities in affected containment units. If a meltdown isn't prevented in time, you will lose energy and affected abnormalities' Qliphoth Counters will drop to 0, so please try to prevent that. You can see more detailed information about Qliphoth Meltdowns in the manual's &lt;Repeated Work Penalty&gt; article.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="42">
      <text>Whenever a Qliphoth Meltdown occurs, the Meltdown Level increases. The higher the Meltdown Level, the more containment units that will be affected by the Qliphoth Meltdown. There is also a chance of an Ordeal appearing instead of a meltdown happening. To learn more about Ordeals, please consult the manual's &lt;Ordeal&gt; article.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="43">
      <text>I think I've told you almost everything about managing abnormalities. If you wish to read more about it, please look it up in the manual. You can consult it at any time during management by pressing F1. Now finish this management day by pressing the Complete button at the top.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="44">
      <text>After finishing each management day, employees who performed work will have their stats increase according to the types of work they performed. After a stat passes a certain point, its level will increase. Employee level can also increase after enough stat increases. Employees who level up are considered promoted and are shown in the list below.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="45">
      <text>You will also be rewarded with LOB for your work according to your management rank. The more employees that survive the day, the higher your management rank. The higher your management rank, the more LOB you receive. If an abnormality is loose when you finish the day, however, you will lose some LOB you would otherwise earn.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="46">
      <text>You can see missions you succesfully completed today in the list here. When you succesfully complete a mission, you can conduct research at the start of the next day. Note that progress does not carry over from day to day: missions must be completed in one day or they will restart the next day.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="47">
      <text>After finishing the management day, you can choose to proceed to the next day or retry this day. Dead employees and destroyed E.G.O Equipment are recovered when you retry, but you will lose observations, PE-Boxes, newly extracted E.G.O Equipment and any promotions employees received for their work on this day.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="48">
      <text>Now please click Skip to Next Day. I will tell you about deployment next.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="49">
      <text></text>
    </node>
  </step>

  <step index ="2">
    <node idx ="0">
      <!-- for timer -->
    </node>

    <node idx ="1">
      <text>When you succesfully manage to clear a mission on the previous day, you can conduct research. Proposals for research are then displayed at the start of the day. You can select one and conduct the research by clicking and dragging it to the slot in the lower right, then hitting OK. Please try to do so with this example research purposal.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="2">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="3">
      <text>Do you recall how much LOB you received during management the other day? You can see the total amount of LOB you have left over here. During this tutorial phase, I will show you how you can spend your LOB, how you can hire new employees and how you can set them up for deployment.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="4">
      <text>Let's start with hiring new employees. Try pressing the Hire button.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="5">
      <text>Here you can see the information and looks of your soon to be new employee. You can increase one of the four state values before hiring them by clicking the arrow button next to it. If for example you wish to hire an employee that has more HP, you can increase its Fortitude. Please try doing this.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="6">
      <text>As you increase the state values of an employee before hiring, the amount of LOB required to hire them will increase as well. The higher the values, the more LOB it will cost. You may need to review how much LOB you are willing to spend on one employee as well as how much you have left after ward before finalizing your decisions.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="7">
      <text>Once you finish setting the employee the way you want it, you can press the Hire button again to hire the employee. Please do so now.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="8">
      <text>You now have hired a new employee. Let's take a look at it's status and information. Please click on the employee.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="9">
      <text>Just like during management, the information displayed about the employee here is the same. If you think your employee could use an increase in a state value, you can still do so by reinforcing the employee. Please press on the Reinforcement of Employee button.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="10">
      <text>And just like when hiring a new employee, you can increase a state value here by pressing the arrow next to it. Like before it will cost LOB when you do this, so keep that in mind. Try increasing the prudence by 1.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="11">
      <text>Now, to finish the reinforcement, press confirm.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="12">
      <text>Your new employee seems ready to be dispatched. Let's try to do this. Click and drag the employee with the primary mouse button over to one of the slots in the Central Command Team.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="13">
      <text>Well done. Now lets give to it some equipment. Remember that we extracted some E.G.O Equipment from the abnormality the previous day? We can give those to the employees. Please press the E.G.O List button.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="14">
      <text>Currently displayed in the center is the list of available E.G.O Weapons you collected and some information about them. Now click on one of the employees you have which shown in the list on the right to select it.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="15">
      <text>Good. You can now equip E.G.O Weapon to the selected employee by pressing one of the empty slots under Equippability.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="16">
      <text>Now let's look at the list of E.G.O Suits we have available. Please press on the E.G.O Suit tab.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="17">
      <text>Like before, you can equip one of the available E.G.O Suits by pressing one of the empty slots.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="18">
      <text>Please try equipping the other employees with both an E.G.O Weapon and E.G.O Suit.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="19">
      <text>Excellent. Now lets head back to the deployment screen. Please press Leave.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="20">
      <text>Looks like there is a Mission here that you can clear on this day. You don't nessecarily have to clear it, but it is recommended since it would allow you to conduct research the next day.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="21">
      <text>One more thing. If you have any questions before starting the management process again, you can review the manual by hitting the button on top. You can also view the manual from the menu displayed when pressing ESC.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="22">
      <text>Next I will tell you briefly how to deal with emergiency situations that can occur during management. When you're ready for that, please press the Start button.</text>
    </node>
  </step>

  <step index ="3">
    <node idx ="0">
      <!-- for timer -->
    </node>

    <node idx ="1">
      <text>Let me explain to you how to deal with emergiency situations. The number displayed here is called a Qliphoth Counter. It will decrease when you do something that violates the guidelines displayed at Managerial Works on the abnormality's information screen or fail to avert the Qliphoth Meltdown in time.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="2">
      <text>Are you wondering now what would happen when the Qliphoth Counter of an abnormality hits 0? Let's find out. Please select the containment unit and order an employee to do Repression work.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="3">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="4">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="5">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="6">
      <text>When an abnormality's Qliphoth Counter hits 0, the abnormality will either escape or use a special ability. This can lead to inconvenient situations. This particular abnormality happens to escape under this condition. Employees can't work with it when it is escaped, so we'll need to Suppress it. Please select the escaped abnormality.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="7">
      <text>Abnormalities have four different types of damage they can inflict on employees. RED which decreases Health (HP), WHITE which decreases Sanity (SP), BLACK which decreases both HP and SP and PALE, which decreases Health by percentages based on the target's maximum HP. Employees equipped with E.G.O Weapons can also utilize one of these 4 damage types.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="8">
      <text>Abnormalities also have a set of defenses based on the damage types. Some type of damage might be weaker while others may be fatal to them. You can suppress an abnormality more effectively when your employees attack using the type of damage the abnormality is weak against. </text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="9">
      <text>This abnormality deals RED damage and is weak to WHITE damage. Conveniently, our employees are all equipped with E.G.O Suits that offer resistance against RED damage and carry E.G.O Weapons that deal WHITE damage.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="10">
      <text>One more thing, if the employee carries a E.G.O Weapon which E.G.O Level is higher than the abnormality's Risk Level, they will deal more damage to the abnormality and take less damage from it. In the current situation, the E.G.O Level and Abnormality's Risk Level are the same, so currently this does not apply.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="11">
      <text>When the suppression window is displayed, you can see what type of damage an employee will deal on the target before sending an order and when you hover your mouse over the employee, you will be able to see their defenses against the four types of damage abnormalities can inflict. Now please, choose an employee to conduct the suppression of this escaped abnormality.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="12">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="13">
      <text>Meeting an abnormality, especially when it is on the loose can be quite shocking and frightening for your employees. Just like when they enter a containment unit to do work on an abnormality, it could damage their Sanity. If the Risk Level of the abnormality is High compared to the employee's Level, it will cause a greater stain on their mind and lower their SP.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="14">
      <text>It looks like this abnormality might be a bit too strong to suppress for just one employee. Be careful by the way, if an employee dies, the E.G.O Equipment they were using will be lost as well. Let's order the rest of the employees to help suppress this abnormality. Please select the other two employees by clicking and dragging with the primary mouse button.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="15">
      <text>Now click on the abnormality with the secondary mouse button to immediately order them to suppress it. It's a lot safer and easier to give orders such as these when you Pauze. You can Pauze by pressing the icon in the lower left, or by pressing the Space Bar on your keyboard.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="16">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="17">
      <text>You did well handling this situation. Now let’s move these employees to the main room in the department. Select them all by clicking and dragging with the primary mouse button.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="18">
      <text>While they’re selected click the main room with secondary mouse button. You can use this method to move them to other places as well by the way, such as hallways and other departments.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="19">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="20">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="21">
      <text>When an employee has lost all of their sanity points (SP) they will panic. A panicked employee will show different behavior from a regular one and cannot be controlled. What they will do depends on their highest level state value. If you wish to learn more about this please refer to the &lt;Employee Panic&gt; article in the manual. Please click the panicked employee with primary mouse button.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="22">
      <text>Employees can be recovered from their panic when their SP is restored to 100%. You can restore their SP by attacking the employee with WHITE or BLACK damage dealing weapons. Conveniently, all the available employees are equipped with weapons that deal WHITE damage. Please select all available employees and order them to suppress the panicked employees.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="23">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="24">
      <text>That was excellent. Well done. If you ever get into a situation you'd wish to redo, such as reversing the damage that was done, you can do so by pressing ESC and click Return to Memory Repository or by clicking on Retry. When you choose Return to Memory Repository, you can go back to the last day the Memory was Imprinted into the Repository. When you do so, acquired E.G.O Equipment and abnormality observation details will remain with you. Retry doesn’t do that, but it does let you start from the current day’s deployment process.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="25">
      <text>Now let's call all employees back to the main room of the department. You can do this by selecting all of them and using secondary click on the desired location, but when you just want them all back in the main room, there is an easier way. Next to the regenerator guage there is a Return button. You can use this button to call back the employees assigned to the department to the respective main room. Please try doing so.</text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="26">
      <text></text>
    </node>

    <node idx ="27">
      <text>This wraps up our basic manager education and training sessions. If you have any questions during the management process, please refer to the manual by pressing F1. If you want to know what certain aspects of the user interface mean, hover your mouse over them and take a look at the tool tip displayed. Manager, I wish you luck and good health on the job.</text>
    </node>
  </step>

</root>
<!-- 씬 분리할지 안할지 미정
이전 DAY에서 미션을 완료했다면 지금처럼 연구를 진행할 수 있습니다. 연구 제안서를 마우스 좌클릭으로 집은 후 드래그하여 넣어주세요.
지난 관리에서 획득한 LOB이 보이시나요? 현재 보유한 LOB은 이곳에서 확인할 수 있습니다. 이번에는 LOB을 사용하여 직원을 고용하고 배치하는 방법을 가르쳐드리겠습니다.
고용 버튼을 누르세요.
고용 시 직원의 능력치를 올릴 수 있습니다. 직원의 용기 등급을 1 올려주세요.
직원의 능력치를 올릴 경우 고용 비용이 높아집니다. 보유한 LOB을 고려하며 직원을 고용해주세요.
직원의 설정이 완료되었으면 고용 버튼을 다시 한번 누르세요.
새로운 직원이 고용되었습니다. 고용된 직원의 정보를 확인해볼까요? 직원을 클릭해주세요
관리 파트 때와 마찬가지로 직원을 클릭하여 직원의 정보를 확인할 수 있습니다. 직원의 능력치 중 부족한 능력치가 있을 경우 직원 강화를 통해 능력치를 올릴 수 있습니다. 직원 강화를 클릭해주세요.
직원 강화도 고용 때와 마찬가지로 원하는 능력치의 화살표를 눌러 해당 능력치를 올릴 수 있습니다. 직원의 지혜 등급을 1 올려주세요.
강화가 완료되었으면 승인 버튼을 누르세요.
고용된 직원을 마우스 왼쪽 클릭으로 선택한 후 드래그하여 지휘팀에 배치하세요.
좋아요. 이제 직원들에게 지난 관리에서 제조한 E.GO 장비를 장착시켜보죠. E.G.O LIST 버튼을 눌러주세요.
첫번째 직원을 선택해주세요.
E.G.O 장착 목록의 빈칸을 눌러 직원에게 E.G.O WEAPON을 장착시키세요.
E.G.O SUIT 탭을 눌러 E.G.O SUIT의 목록도 확인해보세요.
마찬가지로 E.G.O 장착 목록의 빈칸을 눌러 직원에게 E.G.O SUIT를 장착시키세요.
이제 나머지 직원에게도 E.G.O를 장비시켜주세요.
잘하셨어요. 다시 배치파트로 돌아가죠. 나가기 버튼을 눌러주세요.
이번 DAY에서 진행할 수 있는 미션입니다. 미션을 완료하면 연구를 진행할 수 있으니 가능한 미션을 꼭 진행해주세요.
마지막으로 관리 시작 전 궁금한 점이 있다면 이 곳을 눌러 메뉴얼을 확인해주세요. 이제 관리를 시작하도록 하겠습니다. 관리 시작 버튼을 눌러주세요.
-->
