<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>

 
  <!-- day41 start -->



 <text id="day41_angela_1">They say the world was a place where you couldn't find happiness with your own method.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_2">That it was a world where you had to fool yourself into thinking that fitting into a structured mold was happiness.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_3">Nobody sought history or religion anymore. No one needed them.</text>
  
  <text id="day41_angela_4">Under the guise of a new technology that was needed in the world, new companies emerged using a technology called Singularity.</text>

  <text id="day41_angela_5">Production of a permanent food supply, manufacturing customized living creatures, cargo would be transported at speeds that made it seem like teleportation, AI that were realer than people, technology to preserve the present by binding time, etc...</text>


  <text id="day41_angela_6">Similar to the food chain, small companies began disappearing or were eaten by larger companies...</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_7">At some point, they were called the Wings of the World, and soon a head rose to control the Wings.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_8">People started to find their purpose for existence from the Wings.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_9">However, the truth was, everyone was slowly melting like the wings of Icarus.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_10">It seems they’re encouraging development of the world for the better, but their nature is same as ours.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_11">There’s always a price to pay. The price that we pay is the shame of the Wings and the disgrace of the world and its people.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_12">Lobotomy’s rival energy corporations aren’t that different from us. Who knows? Maybe they really are earning energy from hell as the rumors say.</text>   
  <text id="day41_angela_13">For mankind, the instinct of life and death coexist.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_14">The Wings only guided our instinct of life.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_15">If one instinct dominated too much, the other instinct would begin to make its move slowly and unknowingly from the depths.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_16">Soon a world where everyone wants to return to nothing will arrive.</text>
  
  <text id="day41_angela_17">Into the stillness of silence before mankind was born.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_18">She who loved sunshine wanted to give hope to mankind but failed.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_19">When the hand that only wanted to embrace with warmth was ruthlessly cut off, you clutched the void, and saw the crack between the boundaries that were never shown to others.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_20">Left alone, you decided to instill possibilities to all mankind.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_21">Hope and despair are intertwined in that possibility, making it impossible for anyone to know the answer.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_22">"If all repressed things can be extracted from the earth..." You said to yourself.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_23">In those days, you really looked terrible.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_24">Many coworkers were worried about you and tried to comfort you, but you didn't care or listen to anything.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_25">I guess you still needed your coworkers at some point.</text>
  <text id="day41_angela_26">Seeing as you were the one who locked them in here, barely holding onto the husks of their dead bodies...</text>
  










</localize>
