<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>

 
  <!-- day36 start -->




  <text id="day36_angela_1">Nice to see you again A.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2">I hope you enjoyed your trip.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_3">Did you know that there's been a lot happening since you've been gone?</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_4">Honestly, it wasn't hard replacing you.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_5">If you have any questions, I will answer them freely.</text>
  <text id="day36_selection1">What's happening outside?</text>
  <text id="day36_selection2">How many attempts have we made?</text>
  <text id="day36_selection3">What's going to happen moving forward?</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_1">Those heads and eyes are still watching us through the tuners and gazers/</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_2">The Wings are still flapping towards their sun, not realizing their feathers are melting away.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_3">Our branches are still providing a steady supply of energy without any major incidents.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_4">In the back alleys, the cleaners and fixers are living their lives covered in vomit.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_5">People from the outskirts are still crying out to break into the city.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_6">Finally those within the city have started throwing their lives away, just to be a part of the Wing.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_7">Yes, the world hasn't changed a bit since you left.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_1_8">Once in a while when I look outside, the world still remains so unchanged. It's as if the flow of time in here is futile, being for naught. Even impatience wanes away.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2_1">How many times have you repeated this before?</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2_2">I’m curious, but numbers have little importance to us.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_2_3">Let's just say that number is too vast to ruminate over.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_3_1">There are still lots of tasks you must do.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_3_2">Things that no one else can do.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_6">Unfortunately, we don't have much time left.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_7">The countdown will begin soon.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_8">As you have already experienced, there have been many countdowns in our world.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_9">For destruction or for a new beginning... </text>
  <text id="day36_angela_10">I seem to smile a lot more during this time.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_11">Oh yes, let's just say this smile is because I am happy to see you again.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_12">There are still things you haven't realized yet.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_13">Let me give you a hint.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_14">"For what reason did you go through all the trouble of making this monstrous and horrifying prison?"</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_15">In time, I hope you find the answer on your own.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_16">I cannot help you with this, otherwise, it wouldn't be a prison.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_17">Soon you will meet the Sephirahs on the lower floors. Those who plays a crucial role in Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_18">I don't think you need an explanation about them.</text>
  <text id="day36_angela_19">However, let's make this clear. They've really missed you while you were gone.</text>
</localize>
