<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id="300110">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 is going into $0's containment unit to begin the task. 
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">D-09-104</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Sprites/Unit/creature/ReverseClock</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Backward Clock
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        WAW
      </riskLevel>

      <openText>
        Have you fallen to the lowest bottom?
      </openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {<i>This Abnormality is made based on the idea of the Tumblbug backer '정현교(Jung Hyunkyo)'</i>&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;An old clock manufactured by an unknown company. It vacuum tubes that give off vintage vibe. The manufacturer stopped making these long ago.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {“…Is your future dark? Have you fallen to the lowest bottom? Have you ever thought, ‘What if I had done or not done that”?&#13;&#10;We, as humanity, have conquered diseases and nature. Now, we have come far enough to harnessing time itself. }
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Yes, we can rewind your wasted time.&#13;&#10;Just wind the spring, close your eyes, and count to ten.&#13;&#10;When you open your eyes, you will be standing in the exact moment that you wished to be in."}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="2">
      [
      {* Read the manual thoroughly. We do not know what will happen if this machinery is handled poorly. We are not responsible for any accidents caused by the user’s carelessness. &#13;&#10;	This clock requires high amount of energy to operate. Please understand that it will take considerable time to charge.}
      ]
    </desc>


    <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">A light turns off and energy is charged for every work done on $0.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">Nothing happened when an employee whose level is lower than 3 worked on it.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="3">After every light has turned on, $0 can be activated. However, $0 could only be operated once a day, so use caution when using it.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="4">&lt;Caution&gt;Employees under level 5 is strictly forbidden from contacting $0 after it is fully charged.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="5">Employee with level 5 or more can operate $0 normally. $0 will send everyone except the employee who activated it to the most peaceful time of that day.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>


  </observe>
</creature>