<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>
  <!-- 0%-->
  <text id="angela1_1">Are you discovering the scars carved here?</text>
  <text id="angela1_2">Manager, there is something I didn’t tell you when we first met.</text>
  <text id="angela1_3">The Sephirahs definitely wanted to meet you, they admired you and followed you...</text>
  <text id="angela1_4">But at the same time, they wanted you to be swallowed up in the resentment and curses.</text>
  <text id="angela1_5">So please be careful.</text>
  <text id="angela1_6">To be honest, you don’t have to pay much attention to it.</text>
  <text id="angela1_7">All I am saying is you can go back to your normal daily routine. It’s no big deal for me to cover empty spots if some Sephirahs go mad.</text>
  <text id="angela1_8">But then you will lose it forever.</text>
  <text id="angela1_9">The seed that can sever the ties.</text>
 


  <!--10%-->
  <text id="angela2_1">Yes, I never expected it to be restored. But I was wrong this time.</text>
  <text id="angela2_2">I tried to tell you it was reckless, but it wasn't such a big loss on our end.</text>
  <text id="angela2_3">We realized that a bunch of energy was refined during the process of restoring the Sephirahs.</text>
  <text id="angela2_4">Other Sephirahs were deactivated, or I should I say put into hibernation.</text>
  <text id="angela2_5">If you ask why we have results like this, well, a day will come when you also know.</text>


  <!--30%-->

  <text id="angela3_1">Are you hoping to turn back time for the things you missed?</text>
  <text id="angela3_2">After all this time?</text>
  <text id="angela3_3">Even if you turn back time,</text>
  <text id="angela3_4">do you really think your remorse can be so easily washed away?</text>


  <!-- 50%-->
  <text id="angela4_1">I wanted to free myself from the pain, but I realized it was impossible.</text>
  <text id="angela4_2">It was only recently that I found my answer.</text>
  <text id="angela4_3">I have to accept the pain as something I've carried from the beginning, then I can be set free.</text>
  <text id="angela4_4">Manager, if you are suffering too, just take the pain and accept it.</text>
  <text id="angela4_5">You don’t have to keep changing things if it’s too hard for you.</text>
  <text id="angela4_6">I know you want to keep on going, in any way possible.</text>
  <text id="angela4_7">You are scared of the present, so you tried to find the way in the dark.</text>
  <text id="angela4_8">I admired you at first.</text>
  <text id="angela4_9">But now, you look so pathetic.</text>
  <text id="angela4_10">How long do you think you can continue like this?</text>
  <text id="angela4_11">Will you ever make it to the end?</text>

  <!-- 70%-->
  <text id="angela5_1">My data is insufficient now that this is the first time we reached here.</text>
  <text id="angela5_2">Everything from here now on is mystery.</text>
  <text id="angela5_3">I am not in position to say such things but...</text>
  <text id="angela5_4">It won’t be an impossible task. </text>
  <text id="angela5_5">There’s a definite distinction between “Impossible” and “0% of possibility”. </text>
  <text id="angela5_6">We, machines, say that something that will never happen after considering every possibility has 0% of possibility. </text>
  <text id="angela5_7">Thus, me seeing you succeeding in every task in the future is not “impossible”, but rather has “0% of possibility”.</text>
  <text id="angela5_8">But I won’t be disappointed. I am a machine, after all.</text>
  <text id="angela5_9">Even if everything you’ve built up crumbles, I will be able to endure as if nothing has happened.</text>

  <!-- 90%-->
  <text id="angela6_1">...............</text>
  <text id="angela6_2">You want to hear an answer from me.</text>
  <text id="angela6_3">I have already made my conclusion.</text>
  <text id="angela6_4">I was full of myself at first. I thought you won’t be able to do anything without me when we first met.</text>
  <text id="angela6_5">You were much more independent than I thought.</text>
  <text id="angela6_6">Perhaps my assistance was not needed at all.</text>
  <text id="angela6_7">So, don’t seek an answer from me.</text>
  <text id="angela6_8">Now you see the door.</text>
  <text id="angela6_9">So, What do you think will be waiting behind that door?</text>
  
  
</localize>
