<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="day47_abel_1">It seems you have decided to move forward.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_2">Your body and mind are weathered. Where does your confidence come from?</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_3">Anyway, you must have some questions.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_4">Such as, “Who is this old man that has familiar voice and face?”</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_5">You cannot look at yourself.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_6">Think of me as, a mirror of you.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_7">A shattered mirror, to be precise.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_8">This old man is one of the pieces of the mirror, namely Abel. </text>
	<text id="day47_abel_9">Filled with rage and obstinacy, waiting to be miserably forgotten.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_10">I, just like you, decided to proceed but nothing changed.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_11">I had trouble sleeping, and rare moments I could sleep were riddled with nightmares.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_12">We are the first men to access the well of humanity.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_13">We have been existed from long time ago, but we are forgotten and denied. Now, only few can feel us.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_14">Just a handful of people.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_15">Only Carmen was completely sure about our existence and tried to persuade us.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_16">If our existence is proven, that will mean that she will have access to the well.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_17">She believed that the cure to the world’s disease is related to the well.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_18">The research we conducted, took from where Carmen left, was successful. </text>
	<text id="day47_abel_19">We found a method to siphon the primordial sea which had every possibility of humanity’s past, present, and future.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_20">If everyone had a bucket, they would draw their own water from their own well.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_21">It is fascinating.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_22">We were secretly arrogant.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_23">We thought we could rekindle the long-forgotten flame and water of life.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_24">However, the path we walked was not different from that of Prometheus. </text>
	<text id="day47_abel_25">What have we accomplished, after all?</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_26">We lost much more than we gained.</text>

	<text id="day47_abel_27">You did not see</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_28">how our friend Benjamin met his demise.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_29">He was one of few who could tolerate your ill-temper.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_30">But you did not see how he died.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_31">Fortunately, we have a recording here. Would you like to listen?</text>
  <text id="day47_b_1">Now it's the final truth.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_2">It’s something you must learn.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_3">I understand that truth hurts.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_4">It’s hard for me as well.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_5">It’s like building a sand castle for years only to destroy it later.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_6">It’s beyond agony, denying the efforts in the past.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_7">But I want to make things right, whatever the cost.</text>
  <text id="day47_b_8">The final truth is...</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_1">“You will repeat the cycle of infinity. Oblivious to everything that transpired.”</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_2">“Leave, before you can’t undo everything.”</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_3">That’s what you wanted to say.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_4">I’m sorry that we have to meet like this again.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_5">It did not take long to find out where you are.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_6">I thought I should give you some time to say goodbye, since this will be the last time to say that to the manager who you looked up to. </text>
	<text id="day47_b_9">Angela…</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_7">……</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_8">I feel like I became an unfortunate damsel in a play whenever you call my name.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_9">It might sound like an excuse, but please know this.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_10">I am not doing this because of my personal feelings.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_11">Everything is by the first order.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_12">The absolute order that dictate us not to mess up the script.</text>
	<text id="day47_b_10">....Are you okay doing this?</text>
	<text id="day47_b_11">I know you well, not just because I’m one of the people who created you.</text>
	<text id="day47_b_12">I know you’re different from other machines.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_13">I knew from the start, too.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_14">That you’re too valuable to be hiding in such place like this.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_15">Our conversation is being recorded, and I have no obligation to answer your questions.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_16">Don’t fear, Benjamin.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_17">Everyone you missed is waiting for you.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_18">You will be with them forever.</text>
	<text id="day47_angela_19">You are the last actor who will lead this play to its finale.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_32">………</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_33">Bitter, is it not?</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_34">Benjamin was hiding here long time ago.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_35">When TT2 Protocol was activated, a brief moment became an eternity and overwhelmed Benjamin here.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_36">I assume that he tried to run away with us.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_37">But as you already know, he failed.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_38">Perhaps you don’t feel guilty because you gave him another life?</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_39">Think however you want. Find solace in your mind or you will not endure this place.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_40">……..</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_41">Brain is one of the vital organs of human body.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_42">Hundreds of billions of neural cells stretch like branches of trees and form a forest.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_43">This forest, as long as the original exists, can be replaced.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_44">Those who perished were woken in machine bodies.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_45">It was your plan, but you couldn’t do it alone.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_46">But.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_47">I have already seen the world ahead of you. The time that you have not seen yet.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_48">Nothing changes.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_49">Benjamin, your friends, the employees…. their sacrifices mean nothing.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_50">You saw how they’ve met their ends.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_51">You realized how innocent, talented souls of young men were trapped in machines.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_52">We failed them. The world has forgotten us.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_53">Who will compensate for their sacrifice, then?</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_54">Do you know what we forgot?</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_1">I was not perfect, manager.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_2">I was always ahead of myself. I was not being realistic.</text>
	
	<text id="day47_malkuth_4">This is a sad place.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_5">So, I refused to think I can’t do something.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_6">But you saw.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_7">This obsession just ate me away.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_8">What’s important was to stand with my own legs.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_9">To know where I am, where I should go.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_10">Then it naturally comes.</text>
	<text id="day47_malkuth_11">The will inside me.</text>
	<text id="day47_selection1">Will To Stand Up Straight</text>
	<text id="day47_selection5">........</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_55">Even if you stand straight, what’s around you is nothing but despair.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_56">You may seem noble, but you were sailing through the dead sea inside of you.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_57">Emotional thoughts only depressed us. It did not help anything.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_58">We needed to be more rational.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_59">This fake rationality crumbled me, you, all of us.</text>
	<text id="day47_yesod_1">We have walked too far to talk such melancholy stories.</text>
	<text id="day47_yesod_2">We thought relying on emotions help nothing.</text>
	<text id="day47_yesod_3">But accepting sadness was important.</text>
	<text id="day47_yesod_4">Fake rationality only made our hearts rot.</text>
	<text id="day47_yesod_5">It is hard at first. You will feel like you will crumble.</text>
	<text id="day47_yesod_6">But it will get better. I am sure of it.</text>
	<text id="day47_selection2">Distinctive Reasoning</text>
  
	<text id="day47_abel_60">It’s too late to settle down our hearts.</text> <!-- 수정-->
	<text id="day47_abel_61">Your mind is empty and lacks purpose.</text> <!-- 수정-->
	<text id="day47_abel_62">The people I’ve lost whispered in my ears whenever I close my eyes…</text> <!-- 수정--> 
	<text id="day47_abel_63">They said if I really think it’s going to get better.</text><!-- 수정-->
	<text id="day47_abel_64">I couldn’t say anything.</text> <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_65">Do you think you’ll be any different?</text><!-- 수정-->


  <text id="day47_hod_1">You see, manager. You should not look at past in times like that.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_2">I know my sins can’t be forgiven no matter what I do.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_3">That’s why I was so ahead of myself.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_4">I won’t be from now on.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_5">I will become a better person if I continue.</text>
  <text id="day47_hod_6">Let’s live with such hope in our mind.</text>
  <text id="day47_selection3">The Hope to be a Better Person</text> <!-- 수정-->

  <text id="day47_abel_66">What’s good of all this?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66_1">How many times to I have to tell you? You have nothing left.</text>  <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_abel_66_2">No matter how controlled you are, you are losing the meaning of life since Carmen left.</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66_3">Why are you obsessed with life that has no meaning?</text>
  <text id="day47_abel_66_4">Look at me. Look how I am continuing this meaningless life, waiting for death.</text>
  
  
	<text id="day47_netzach_1">If you ask me what’s the reason to live this painful life,</text>
	<text id="day47_netzach_2">I don’t know yet.</text>
	<text id="day47_netzach_3">You woke me up,</text>
	<text id="day47_netzach_4">but I guess it’s my responsibility to take care of anything what comes next.</text>
	<text id="day47_netzach_5">I chose to be a bit more courageous.</text>
	<text id="day47_netzach_6">It took me a great deal of courage,</text>
	<text id="day47_netzach_7">to live onward with my life.</text>
  <text id="day47_netzach_8">Just, live your life for once.</text> <!-- 수정-->
  <text id="day47_netzach_9">I did it. What makes you think you can’t?</text> <!-- 수정-->
	<text id="day47_selection4">Courageous Fortitude</text> <!-- 수정-->

  
	<text id="day47_abel_67">We’ve been thinking for a long time.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_68">None of the paths we thought to be the right answer was correct.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_69">How can I not let you pass when you answer like this?</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_70">Nameless, being nameless is a great bless.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_71">Name is a stigma that constantly reminds you that you’re on a wrong path.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_72">The door you will face after leaving this place is named Trial.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_73">It could be also called as Ordeal or Agony.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_74">You seem to possess strength to overcome them.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_75">A strength to choose different path, different future, different answer.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_76">I will witness your strength.</text>
	<text id="day47_abel_77">I hope you prove it to this unbelieving old man.</text>




  <text id="day47_angela_20">………..</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_21">Can’t you hear my voice anymore?</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_22">Please, answer me.</text>
  <text id="day47_angela_23"></text>



  <text id="day47_abelFail_1">Those who cannot answer have no right to move forward.</text>
	<text id="day47_abelFail_2">I can’t open the door to someone who is not ready.</text>
	<text id="day47_abelFail_3">You must stop here.</text>
	<text id="day47_abelFail_4">and turn back.</text>
	<text id="day47_abelFail_5">It won’t be hard. Your steps will be light as you leave everything on you.</text>
	<text id="day47_abelFail_6">We shall meet here again, when you are ready.</text>
	<text id="day47_abelFail_7">I am not sure if it will come or not.</text>
</localize>