<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="day50_ayin_1">Have you met your reflections?</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_2">They must have tried to stop you because their own tomorrows will not come.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_3">But you gave up on yesterdays with them,</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_4">and finally, we meet today.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_5">You must have realized that. Seeing you have come this far without hesitation.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_6">I knew,</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_6_1">for a long time.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_7">that we all lost our hearts.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_8">I knew. But I did not do anything about it. I’m sure many others did.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_9">...That’s what makes Carmen different from us.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_10">Instead of looking away, she wanted to save them and find their souls back.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_11">She was the one who made the noble decision of saving humanity.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_12">But I, who had no such ambition, had to continue her legacy.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_13">Ironic, isn’t it?</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_14">Perhaps I’m not the right man for this job.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_15">I’ve become just like other wings. Committing atrocities just like them.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_16">Employees have repeated hundreds of thousands of deaths,</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_17">my friends are dead and trapped in the cycle of agony.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_18">I was just sitting and watching, just because I thought I should realize her ideal.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_19">This sin will never be forgiven.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_20">Nontheless,</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_21">We must do this.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_22">If these wrongdoings can cut this vicious cycle,</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_23">I will gladly take this burden.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_24">Our mission is to seed people’s heart.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_25">Everyone has their own light.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_26">Tales are created from them; their very existence is rooted in them. </text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_27">We merely seed. It’s up to them how they bloom it.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_28">What about us?</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_29">Unfortunately, we won’t be able to see what kind forest will be created.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_30">We have one more thing to do.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_1">The thing we did countless times.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_2">…managing abnormalities. </text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_3">You will make it. I know you will.</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_4">Come,</text>
  <text id="day50_ayin_30_5">This will be your last work as a manager.</text>
  
  
	<text id="day50_ayin_31">A tree burst from the land. It scattered fruits onto the world from its branches.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_32">The tree grown from infinite possibilities and processes is closer to the sky and fierce more than anything else.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_33">The lines between past and future, reality and illusion, body and mind, space and time were being slowly fading away.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_34">They say that void awaits at the end,</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_35">but I know that it’s not just empty.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_36">You will be the infinite light.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_37">Your name is Ayin.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_38">Remember our names.</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_39">and…</text>
	<text id="day50_ayin_40">Fade away.</text>
  
  
  
 
</localize>