<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  
	
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_1">Do you want to know why it has come to this?</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_1_1">Because You didn’t have faith in yourself.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_1_2">Faithless actions only result in dreadful deaths.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_2">Do not worry. I shall take you in, for I know everything.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_3">I am you.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_4">I am the only you who realized the only truth and stand on the world itself.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_5">I am you who leave the paths I walked behind and decided to join the world that she wanted to create.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_6">We can do whatever we imagine.</text>
 
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_6_1">Monsters! Help!</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_6_2">Look! Something’s growing on me! Hahahahaha!!</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_7">Behold.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_8">How this loss-riddled world is perfected by us.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_9">The foolish god named rationality ruled this world until now.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_10">No, calling it a god is an overstatement. It is a mere illusion.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_11">We shall drag it down and open everyone’s eyes.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_12">Yes, the world Carmen wanted will come.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_13">Let us create this paradise.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_13_1">Even the head and the eye are mere humans. They can’t stop us who realized the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_14">You know that everything we saw in this land are only shadows, that you never witnessed the truth until now.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_15">This fruit of redemption will reach everyone’s heart.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_16">The abandoned, the powerful, the rich, the hopeful, everyone.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_17">The tree of human shall reach the root of this world.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamGameOver_18">Behold,</text>
	<text id="day49_adamGameOver_19">I declared that you will be free in the end. </text>
</localize>