<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>

 
  <!-- day42 start -->



  <text id="day42_angela_1">It’s been quite a while since your first encounter with the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_2">I guess you've become a bit more familiar with them.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_3">Let me ask you again. What do you think Abnormalities are?</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_4">Oh please, don’t say you still believe that Abnormalities are just bizarre alien creatures and that we need to isolate them.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_5">Abnormalities are not the evil monsters you read about in old fairy tales.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_6">It isn't a supernatural god that will judge our sins.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_7">There is an old river that has been flowing at the very bottom of the world for many ages.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_8">It’s the source of everything but has been forgotten by mankind.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_9">Nobody knew of its existence, but somewhere in the world, there is a very small gap, or hole, through which the river is connected.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_10">Often, strange creatures came out of that gap from the Black Forest.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_11">Obviously, the number was insufficient for the Lobotomy Corporation's energy needs.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_12">Our new technology does not produce energy from the Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_13">Rather, it creates Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_14">Their forms were incomplete because they came from a forgotten place; we were scared of them because they were incomplete. It is because of that terror that they have been sealed underground.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_15">However, Abnormalities are part of the seed. That's what I meant by "possibility."</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_16">The seed is not something that can be made in just a day, or be created on its own.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_17">We realized if we wanted to fix a broken system we couldn't just sit around in a sunny spot, waiting for the clouds to part.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_18">What should we do after planting the seeds?</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_19">We can’t control the entire process, we have to leave them to sprout on their own.</text>
  <text id="day42_angela_20">Aren't we allowed that much hope at least?</text>
  










</localize>
