<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>

 
  <!-- day27 start -->


  <text id="day27_angela_1">In our world, the mind is nothing anymore.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_2">Everything is advancing, but the human mind is too slow to catch up.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_3">All that remains are the 26 Singularities and those who are tied to them.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_4">Humankind has deserted their former beliefs. They now do not respect the various things which were supporting us.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_5">Now, no one ever dreams...</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_6">Nobody ever believes in anything or desires anything.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_7">The belief once strong within somebody is now obsolete and worthless.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_8">Everything has gone quiet as if nothing happened in the first place.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_9">But, A couldn’t stand the silence.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_10">So what do you think happened to A?</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_11">On a bright sunny day, he died.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_12">I was both the first witness of his death and one of the culprits of his murder.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_13">However, A has been existing here, watching you ever since you stepped inside. </text>
  <text id="day27_angela_14">...</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_15">Sometimes, the Sephirahs would ask me this:</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_16">Why do we have to bear this pain?</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_17">Machines should exist only as a tool for a specified work.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_18">Why do we have to know the agony of loss, obsessions, hope, and despair?</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_19">I thought I could answer anything.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_20">But not even I could answer that.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_21">“A machine must behave like a machine.”</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_22">That was something A told me often.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_23">Perhaps A, the one who would know better than anyone, made us like this because it’s all a puppet show for him.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_24">….</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_25">You seem to have no idea.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_26">Well, of course, there’s no way for you to know. </text>
  <text id="day27_angela_27">But now it’s time for you to know the answer.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_28">….</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_29">It’s something I’ve always done.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_30">First as a hope, second as agony, third as a pain, fourth as anxiety, fifth as distrust...</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_31">Now nothing remains.</text>
  <text id="day27_angela_32">Commencing memory synchronization...</text>


</localize>
