<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>

 
  <!-- day46start -->

  <text id="day46_abel_1">A long time has passed since my loved ones have left with their broken bodies and hearts.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_2">We’ve finally met, after taking a long detour…</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_3">I sent you a letter someday.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_4">That old, strange letter that had the same name on “sender” and “recipient”.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_5">It told you that we will meet soon.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_6">……..</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_7">Why are you hesitating? Come, with your mind at ease. </text>
  <text id="day46_abel_8">I hope this environment satisfies you. I tried my best to recreate our office.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_9">You need at least one place to feel comfortable, don’t you?</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_10">However, I speculate that you felt that this place is a bit more…serene than you might remember.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_11">There are many reasons to that.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_12">This is the reflection of your heart, after all. </text>
  <text id="day46_abel_13">We weren’t particularly fond of untidiness. However, there was she, who made a mess out of an organized room.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_14">There were times we were used to such messiness, giving up on cleaning the room.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_15">But, sadly, our hearts couldn’t take those moments in. </text>
  <text id="day46_abel_16">I am sure now you know</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_17">that this space changes to your heart.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_18">This office is born from your heart, siphoned up from your deepest unconsciousness.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_19">Yes, many parts of this facility were extracted and created from our minds.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_20">How did you think building such enormous underground structures in such short period of time was possible?</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_21">We needed multiple extractions until we finally solidified something that had no form.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_22">We repeated so many times, until the memories were blurred, and sins were forgotten.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_23">Yes, there were a lot of repeats.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_24">It must have been roughly 10 years outside, while this entire facility has been trapped in the cycle in length of one hundred thousand years.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_25">This eternity is fascinating.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_26">All humans only live once.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_27">The future comes to us like relentless waves of sea.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_28">We cannot go against them. We are merely pushed back by them. </text>
  <text id="day46_abel_29">Time Track’s technology could only reverse time in a very limited area.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_30">This tech was used to trivial things, such as granting the infinite moments of death to a condemned,</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_31">or showing those whose times are numbered their happiest times.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_32">However, when combined with our energy tech, this small technology could bloom into something bigger.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_33">We invested on them without hesitation, even though they required massive amount of funding and energy.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_34">That’s how Time Track’s second invention came to life.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_35">If time can be reversed infinitely, we could reach the sky which seemed unreachable. </text>
  <text id="day46_abel_36">But sadly, breaking an absolute rule cost us a lot.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_37">The reverse, although it could be executed infinitely, always left some form of distortion. This technology is not perfect yet, either.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_38">No man could have their sanity intact in this place.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_39">But here you are. You reached this point, even though you limped on the way.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_40">Of course, it wouldn’t have been possible if it were not for Angela, but it is a herculean achievement that you went through that journey.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_41">Let your body and mind rest. You must be exhausted.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_42">The path after this will be brutal.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_43">Extremely brutal.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_44">Me and “us” that you will meet again will be also brutal.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_45">They will not let you pass like I do.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_46">By any chance, if you think you’re not ready yet, it is okay to go back to the starting point.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_47">If you have reached here after such a long time,</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_48">you will come again, no matter how long it takes.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_49">We literally have all the time in the world. There is no need to be hurry.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_50">Just keep in mind that situation will be very much different if you move forward from here.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_51">You will be given harsh trials and unanswered, saturated questions.</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_52">And, I think you already know that,</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_53">You can reverse time,</text>
  <text id="day46_abel_54">but you can’t reverse a tale.</text>


 

  










</localize>
