<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  
	<text id="day49_adam_1">Welcome</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_2">You won’t believe how long I have been painstakingly waiting for you.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_3">Ah,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_4">It was so boring.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_5">You know, the world is not interesting anymore to those who realized the greater good.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_6">Think about the world you were in.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_7">Everyday is singularity, everything changes in a blink of an eye.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_8">Wings control the world, and now people can’t live without control.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_9">People just stay silent even though they all know how ethically wrong the wings are.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_10">Those who are not controlled die as a loner and a failure. That’s how we are now.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_11">Who was I in the past, who am I now, who should I be in the future?</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_12">These questions were stopped being asked long time ago. All people have left is to die slowly.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_12_1">Nothing is boring as watching a certain fall.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_13">So,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_14">We found it.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_15">The light that resides in everyone.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_16">Unfortunately, most people don’t find their light in their lifetime.</text>

	<text id="day49_adam_18">Humanity is bound to be unhappy as they just chase illusion without realizing the truth.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_19">People started hiding their lights in deepest part of their heart.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_20">Carmen thought that she should draw such lights.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_21">Yes, we could see the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_21_1">Abnormalities are not illusions.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_21_2">They’re our truer form,</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_22">drawn from the lights in our hearts.</text>

	<text id="day49_adam_23">Abnormalities are the true human of this age. They are our pure form that is shed from our empty skins.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_24">They feared and tried to contain the abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_24_1">Do not blame their ignorance.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_24_2">It was only natural that they feared being naked.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_25">At least you and I know that,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_26">Carmen will be our forbidden apple for the new humanity.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_27">Call my name.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_28">I am Adam, the first of new humanity.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_29">I will wait for the fruits to come to life after I seed this vast forest.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_30">The forbidden apple that will enlighten us all with the knowledge that is branded in our heart but forgotten.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_31">A single bite will open their eyes and grant them wisdom.</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_31_1">They will be free from sins of forgetting what we are,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_32">and ashamed of their skins.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_33">If we draw everyone’s well with bucket, then their ego won’t need to be locked anymore.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_34">Just imagine. Everything that is oppressed burst out in every form possible.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_35">Doesn’t that give you chills?</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_36">We always asked,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_37">how a person should live?</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_38">Nobody could answer.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_39">But I found it. </text>
	<text id="day49_adam_40">I will show you. Join me.</text>
  
	<text id="day49_binah_1">Do you want to know how I could be so cruel?</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_2">People live with their own anxiety.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_3">It’s a natural cost for facing an unknown.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_4">But I did not accept that anxiety and fear. I devoured them to survive in this world.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_5">That is the first and final sin I committed.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_6">I don’t regret it. It was for survival.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_7">Aren’t you the same?</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_8">I knew, seeing your face when you ripped through my brain.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_9">You might say it was inevitable.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_10">You need to face the fear that you have forgotten now.</text>
	<text id="day49_binah_11">If you want to stop the cycle</text>
	
	<text id="day49_selection1">The eye facing the fear, cutting the cycle</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_41">Do you think you can see things clearly? When you couldn’t see them all along?</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_42">You are afraid.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_43">If you think it is a sin to deprive them of act of facing the fear,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_44">listen well,</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_45">If we can conduct thousands of good, one bad is acceptable.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_46">Shedding everyone from their empty skin. Can’t you see how this is the greatest good of all?</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_47">People need someone like us.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_48">Think about the wave of redemption that will follow.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_1">It is in everyone’s instinct to pursue freedom.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_2">Remember the reason why I gladly let you pass.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_3">I did because I wanted to fly with your own strength despite being left in this harsh world.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_4">If we talked more sincerely in the past,</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_5">perhaps it would have been resulted in a better circumstance.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_6">However, we already left our past behind. We cannot go back.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_7">We live in endless conflicts and regrets from the birth to death.</text>
	<text id="day49_hokma_8">We grow by facing them and walk to the future.</text>
	<text id="day49_selection2">The eye embracing the past, creating the future</text>

	<text id="day49_adam_49">You refuse to join me, and move to the unpredictable future?</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_50">Your days will be filled with marvels and wonders if you join me.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_51">You are not even sure if you’re on the right path because it is painful to live day by day.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_52">This sacred secret can’t be wasted like this.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_53">I don’t have a time anymore. If you are not ready, I will be going first.</text>
	<text id="day49_adam_54">..Are you…?</text>
  <text id="day49_adam_55">So you don’t want to stop me, but block me. </text>




  <text id="day49_angela_1">…………….</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_2">You don’t want me to stand by your side at the end of this story.</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_3">I am not among those.</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_4">Those who would face the end together with you…</text>
  <text id="day49_angela_5"></text>


  <text id="day49_adamFail_1">The flesh inside is bound to rot when they're covered in skin that does not fit</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_2">Don’t worry. I shall show for I know everything.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_3">I am you.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_4">I am the only you who realized the only truth and stand on the world itself.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_5">I am you who leave the paths I walked behind and decided to join the world that she wanted to create.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_6">We can do whatever we imagine.</text>
 
  <text id="day49_selection3">.......</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_6_1">Monsters! Help!</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_6_2">Look! Something’s growing on me! Hahahahaha!!</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_7">Behold.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_8">How this loss-riddled world is perfected by us.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_9">The foolish god named rationality ruled this world until now.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_10">No, calling it a god is an overstatement. It is a mere illusion.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_11">We shall drag it down and open everyone’s eyes.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_12">Yes, the world Carmen wanted will come.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_13">Let us create this paradise.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_13_1">Even the head and the eye are mere humans. They can’t stop us who realized the truth.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_14">You know that everything we saw in this land are only shadows, that you never witnessed the truth until now.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_15">This fruit of redemption will reach everyone’s heart.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_16">The abandoned, the powerful, the rich, the hopeful, everyone.</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_17">The tree of human shall reach the root of this world.</text>
  <text id="day49_adamFail_18">Behold,</text>
	<text id="day49_adamFail_19">I declared that you will be free in the end. </text>
</localize>