<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y1">…</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y2">Manager, you represent the company. I think your outfit is not up for the company standard. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y3">I am only a Sephirah, so I can't do anything about it. Just saying.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y4">I am Yesod, the Sephirah of the Information Team. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y5">I am in charge of processing and archiving all the data of the company. We need to concentrate and focus on our job all the time.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y6">Like the curators of a library.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y7">A single mistake from us could cause a disaster.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y8">I am sure you'd understand the gravity of my work.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y9">Every bit of data we have... cost us blood and lives.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y10">You should show some respect. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y11">….</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y12">I am little allergic to... revealing cloths.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y13">I hate revealing cloths.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y14">I don’t know why or since when, though. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y15">Probably before I got into the company.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_n1">Yesod, do you have some spare paper?</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y16">Netzach, you know the rules. We're not supposed to trade stuff between teams.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_n2">Pft, Yesod the Viper is not in a good mood. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y17">...</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_n3">I am leaving, okay?</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y18">Why, is this entertaining to you?</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y19">My apologies. I... overreacted a bit.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y20">Other Sephirahs are just making fun of me.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y21">But I know employees hate me.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y22">I know my nickname is not a positive one.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y23">But I like it, because I earned it on purpose.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y24">It tells others who I am.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y25">What do you think of my nickname?</text>
  <text id="yesod1_selection1">I like it, too.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_selection2">I don’t like it.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y1_1">Then we're on the same page. </text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y2_1">Well, I like it anyway.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y26">I should go now.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y27">I must finish today's work.</text>
  <text id="yesod1_intro_y28">Oh, I will send you the next assignment. </text>


  <!--에피소드 2-->

  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1">You exceeded all my expectations. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2">Let me explain about your next-</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h1">Yesod! I heard about the accident.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y3">How many times is it?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h2">Shouldn't you... be with your team members?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y4">Accidents do happen. I don't want to rub in it. It only encourages them to cry more.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h3">But people are dead! You should say something, even a half-hearted commemorating speech would be better than silence!</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y5">I am not you. I see no point in being sentimental. I am too good to be shackled by cheap emotions. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_h4">Well, I am just saying... I guess there is no right answer. See you around!</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y6">What do you think? Should I go comfort them?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_selection1">Yes, do so.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_selection2">No, that's not necessary.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_1"> Honestly, I am surprised to hear that from you.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_2">You make a speech every time there is an accident?  </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_3">Don't you just watch them shred in pieces in your shiny monitor every day?</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_4">I will blame your inexperience, manager. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y1_5">Sympathy does no good in the company.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_1">Your gesture of 'good will' only fuels their frustration and anger. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_2">You're not the one whose life is on the line. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_3">You don't know how it feels when every moment could be your last.</text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_4">They're so close to death that they do not have hopes for a brighter future.  </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_5">I don't like the way Hod copes with it. She just shuts eyes and as if nothing happened. </text>
  <text id="yesod2_intro_y2_6">Me, I work hard to find ways to minimize casualties.</text>
 
  <!--에피소드 3-->

  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_1">Z... umm. Zoo.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e2_1">Oz!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_2">Oz is an imaginary place! It doesn't count.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y1">… </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_3">Oops, I didn't know you were there, Sephirah.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e2_2">Sorry, I didn't mean to... He insisted...</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e1_4">What? You started it, you wanted revenge, remember?</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_e2_3">Shut it, Dirk!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y2">Go back to your work, now!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_et_1"> Of course, Sephirah. We're sorry!</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y3">Word chain is one of the most popular pastime here.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y4">Do you like the game?</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y5">(Yesod ponders.)</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y6">James, you can’t enter the cell when your stress level is above 80%. It's against rules. </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j1">I know, just this once, please? You know Sally went in at 82% and came out fine! I need this run to meet the quota.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y7">.. </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j2">What are friends for, huh? You know I am on your side no matter what. </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y8">..</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j3">I promise you, just this once.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y9">You know, I am not in the position to make exceptions... </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j4">What's the problem if no one knows? Besides, I gave you some slack yesterday when we were playing word chain.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y10">Fine, but only this once.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y11">And make sure to take the examination after the work. </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_j5">Sure! Thanks, Yesod! You just saved my life! </text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y12">Sometimes I see hallucination when I change my clothes.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y13">My skin... is covered with festering boils... horrible.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y14">Of course, my body is fine when I open my eyes.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y15">What bothers me is... not the hallucination itself.</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y16">It's that feeling... that the hallucination is real and I am deluding myself into believing that I have normal skin...</text>
  <text id="yesod3_intro_y17">I asked other Sephirahs, but I am the only one who experiences this.</text>
  
  <!-- 에피소드 4-->

  <text id="yesod4_intro_y1">James purposefully released two Abnormalities that eventually killed seven people.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y2">Lost the Abnormalities and four employees.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y3">I ordered to shoot down James.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y4">I know what kind of place we're working in.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y5">I am not sorry for the fact that I was unable to stop him.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y6">I am sorry for the fact that I knew him personally.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y7">I let my subordinates exploit me.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y8">The chat, the game, all fun.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y9">And James was a good joker.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y10">Playing word chain was fun, too.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y11">James died because I was weak.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y12">I promised myself not to repeat this error on that day.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y13">Manager, this is Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y14">We see body bags every day.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y15">It's a lonely place. </text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y16">Sometimes you will want to have friends. </text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y17">When you feel lonely, remember what happened to me.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y18">You will be able to get over meaningless deaths.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y19">I envy Angela. She doesn’t have feelings.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y20">People say I am too rational.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y21">They say I am cold-blooded, calculating, and devoid of emotions. I take them as compliments.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y22">I am not in denial, you know.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y23">Whoever built this place is a cruel person.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y24">Sometimes, I want to be an AI without emotion...</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y25">Sympathy clouds your judgment. You are bound to make mistakes.</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y26">Why would anyone place AI with emotion in this cruel facility?</text>
  <text id="yesod4_intro_y27">Do you know the answer?</text>

  <!-- 에피소드 5-->
  <text id="yesod5_intro_h1">Yesod, you feel nothing about this?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_n1">Try drinking some Enkephalin, close your eyes, and open again.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a1">I am glad you are not as weak as the other Sephirahs. It is important to keep a clear head in any situation.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A1">….... Gabriel, why are you scratching yourself like that?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y1">Seeing as we've met again, you must have completed your tasks, manager.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y2">I'd give you a compliment if I didn't have so much work to do.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y3">The Information Team has a work that they must do on specific periods.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y4">You must have realized there are some blanks on the Abnormality Records.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y5">Among the tremendous amount of information we gather, there are some that are off limits to the employees for security reasons.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y6">The names of the employees are one of those information.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y7">All traces of them, what happened to them, their gruesome deaths, their desperate will to live, all of that has been stripped from the records under the pretext of "expunging information."</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y8">I do not know what the criteria are for stripping the records. That is decided by other departments, not us.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y9">We only manipulate the information we receive, per ordered.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y10">Isn’t it funny?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y11">What we do is destroy or manipulate information, but somehow we are still called the "Information Team."</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y12">Whenever I am introduced as a Sephirah of the Information Team,</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y13">I sometimes feel something bubbling up inside me.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a2">Yesod, did you receive the documents to expunge?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a3">You will get the employee list soon as well. Don't forget to be reviewed after you finish expunging the documents.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y14">Angela, what do you think it means to remember someone’s name?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a4">Why are you so emotional today?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y15">Maybe names are like marks for atypical existences to distinguish themselves from others.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y16">Someone might have named you Angela having the same thought.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a5">Yesod, if you are too tired, take a break.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y17">I knew you would say that.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_a6">I’m glad you know.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y18">........</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y19">Calling employees with their names is not recommended here.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y20">When employees enter the company, each one receives their own identification number.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y21">This is to allow the company to identify the minimum necessary information.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y22">We have their numbers in our data storage device.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y23">Malkuth did not call employees by their names from the beginning.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y24">Maybe she is the most ideal Sephirah amongst us all.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y25">I am not saying that it is appropriate for Malkuth to take all the pain as well.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y26">None of us do.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y27">What kind of bad taste is that, to lock us into the metal body, and to make us repeat our days endlessly?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y28">I'm talking to you. What's with that blank expression?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y29">I heard you might be one of our designers.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y30">The only thing I could do here is remember a few names of the forgotten employees, and despair endlessly...</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y31">Feeling sick of even a single breath of air...</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y32">Are you having fun watching your guinea pigs?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y33">......</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_y34">See, I told you, the inside has been rotting for a long time...</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A2">Gabriel was more rational than anyone else.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A3">He was unmoved, even after listening to what happened to Elijah.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A4">Some said he lacked empathy.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A5">But nobody knew he was festering in the inside.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A6">Maybe it started happening from long ago, ever since Carmen the world.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A7">He slowly became expressionless. He did not allow himself to even have paltry joys.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A8">He also could not stand having even a small part of his body being exposed.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A9">We made a monster that was not supposed to exist in this world. We came too far to go back.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A10">To not let what Elijah did go to vain, instead of taking time to grieve, everyone knew they needed to utilize this result to the fullest.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A11">He tried to remain level-headed, but his attempts became an obsession.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A12">He started to wear long sleeved shirts that also covered his neck. Not much later, he started to scratch himself harshly.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A13">We suggested he receive a check-up to see whether he was contaminated or infected, but he refused.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_selection1">Enforce.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_selection2">Enforce.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_selection3">Enforce.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A14">Health check-ups were needed to prevent further damage. Persuasion became compulsion, and compulsion led to the use of physical force.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A15">He was tied up for the check up, but resisted so violently that It was hard for us to watch him.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A16">Eventually, it turned out that he was not infected at all.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A17">But was that really fortunate?</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A18">No, it was not. He didn’t get any better. He kept scratching himself. So badly.. Even worse..</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A19">When I saw him last, he was not cognizant to what anyone said, and his body was covered in scratches.</text>
  <text id="yesod5_intro_A20">No body has seen him since then.</text>

  <!-- 에피소드 6-->

  <text id="yesod6_intro_y1">.... I heard about Elijah, I’m sorry.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y2">I guess now everybody knows there are consequences when forcefully opening an access-controlled laboratory.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y3">Also, you were very careless not to put the supply room key back to its place.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y4">You may think I am being too strict, but I can’t help it. I am not saying anything wrong.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y5">I should set up a time for when keys must be returned to prevent this from happening again.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y6">…………</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y7">I wore this to prevent chemicals from splashing on my body.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y8">I am just a little tired.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y9">Never mind. I will go prepare the next experiment.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A1">Wounds have a way of showing; even for those who wish to keep them concealed.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A2">For Gabriel, it was his clothes.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A3">Maybe he felt better to conclude that Elijah’s death was caused by not following the rules.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A4">He tried harder to stick to principles. He tried to maintain his objectivity.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A5">But perhaps his excessive rationality is what destroyed him.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A6">His earnest hope to not to see anyone else die did not come true.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_A7">No, I don’t want to lie anymore. I pretended that I didn’t hear the shout of desperation.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y10">…………</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y11">No need to ask me if I am doing okay.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y12">I heard about what you and I did.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y13">It was the first time for me to lose myself.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y14">It was not pleasant, but it was not as terrible as I expected it to be.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y15">I rather feel relieved.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y16">I am not saying all the hatred I have is gone.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y17">I will still see the rotting illusion, sometimes feel disgusted, and will feel unbearable anger towards you.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y18">Well, there is one aspect that's changed.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y19">I can be in as much despair as I want to now.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y20">Someday, painful hope will grow out of the rotten wound.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y21">What you gave to us was a seed of hope.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y22">I think you are also on your way to embracing your past.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y23">It's always the beginning that's difficult.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y24">And your outfit is still not acceptable.</text>
  <text id="yesod6_intro_y25">I should seriously consider having penalty points even for managers.</text>
</localize>
