<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>
  <!-- 에피소드 1-->
  
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1">You’re back.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2">Did you have fun while I was locked up here?</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b3">Don't worry, I'm not mad at you.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b4">'Oh, agony! You will never leave me so I came here to honor you.'</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b5">It’s hard to know the flow of time in this place,</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b6">so this eternity saved me.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b7">Have you ever seen shrouds of a huge river that crossed the entire city?</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b8">If you get downstream after the wild rapids and a winding current,</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b9">you will see an enormously broad, but peaceful meadow.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b10">That land is covered with all kinds of mud, sand, and sludge that has come from upstream.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b11">Those which weren't caught by the upper stream and midstream would finally end up here at the bottom.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b12">To receive all the sludge that piles up, I would recommend a strong back that won't break easily.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b13">I have seen many wells here.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b14">I have to draw water every day, but the water level never seems to lower.</text>
  <text id="binah1_selection1">What is a well?</text>
  <text id="binah1_selection2">What does it mean to draw water?</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1_1">The well is so deep that the bottom cannot be seen,</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1_2">and has been the source of all mankind and their relics from ancient times.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b1_3">The water inside the well never has never flowed outside. There have been only a few ripples that permeated from the leaves that fell from the winds.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2_1">Our role is to bring the water that's deep inside the well back to the surface.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2_2">You never know what the bucket might contain from the eternal darkness, but I always drew the water with a pulley, no matter what.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b2_3">Be careful not to fall into the well.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b15">Maybe it was a warning for those who were thirsty trying to quench their thirst,</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b16">but it was you who put the bucket in the well.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b17">But it was not you who poured the water.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b18">Don't ask me for my name.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b19">'Vina' is not a name.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b20">It's the sad name of the place where many graves are located.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b21">I am the one who draws the water.</text>
  <text id="binah1_intro_b22">Why have you come to this place and what do you wish me to draw?</text>

  
  <!--에피소드 2-->

  <text id="binah2_intro_b1">Are you looking at all the tombstones of this place?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b2">It's a sight to see. There have been days where I've spent reading all the meaningless letters written on them.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b3">These are also coffins. It is death itself, but also the possibility of birth.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b4">I have been guarding their coffins for many years. I perform the dedications for those who cannot leave here.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b5">That's one of the few things I do here.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b6">If you spend enough time in the grave,</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b7">you can hear the whispers of the dead.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b8">The sound of their words so dark it makes me feel like I am being filled with black water.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b9">Seeing as you are taking a look around here, you must be starting to get bored.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b10">I don't always have guests and I would feel bad to only show you these tombstones.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e1">Did you call, Binah?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b11">The boundary of this employee had once crumbled.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b12">What’s your name?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e2">My name is.. Nathan.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b13">This one was in charge of extracting E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b14">He happened to see the inside of the well by chance but luckily survived.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b15">He had to pay for looking into the well, but they managed to save him by giving him a maximum dose of Enkephalin. After that, he was able to return to work.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b16">But, once you glimpse through the crack of the boundary, you can never go back to the world where once you belonged.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b17">Do you want to see something interesting?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b18">Nathan, could you tell the manager what you saw and what you had to forget?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e3">From the tombstone... there are..... sleeping people, deep down...</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b19">They are the ones who are dreaming good dreams. At the same time they are called the "well" in the language of this place.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e4">We need to extract them... and inject Cogito...</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b20">Then what? What did you see?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e5">That man... that...</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b21">Keep going.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_e6">He, he....he....h....h.. he.....in... in the well....</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b22">He passed out. Poor thing.</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection1">The reason he passed out is,</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection2">that these people,</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b1_1">they cannot disobey me.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b1_2">And for him to pass out without completing his sentence means that he pushed himself to the limit to obey my orders.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b2_1">Don’t worry. He won’t last even today with a mind as weak as his.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b2_2">It is easier to do nothing and just watch the sands fall away, rather than trying to stop the sand castle from collapsing.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b23">I have been seeing what this child saw, for hundreds, thousands of times, or even more.</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection3">Why am I still here?</text>
  <text id="binah2_selection4">Why am I okay?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b24">Why am I still sane enough to talk with you peacefully?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b25">I can barely contain my spirit thanks to my mechanical body. Yes, the strong back that never breaks.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b26">But, A.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b27">Did you forget I was also born from a human mind?</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b28">......</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b29">However, one good thing,</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b30">even if I go crazy and run amuck destroying everything including you,</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b31">I have her to turn my power off.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b32">But if that day really comes, I would rather you kill me than her.</text>
  <text id="binah2_intro_b33">It's the least you can do, to a confined person as me.</text>


  <!-- 에피소드 3-->
  <text id="binah3_intro_b1">Fierce fights break out every day here, just as you have lived until this moment.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b2">You’ve seen this countless time, haven’t you?</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b3">With enough time, abnormalities come back to life. No matter how many pieces they’re broken into.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b4">It’s one of the facts that drive Gebura mad.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b5">She took too long to realize that abnormalities are to be exploited, not terminated.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b6">Or perhaps, she just couldn’t shake the anger of her past off.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b7">Well, it’s none of my business. All I know is that I will never see old her again.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b8">Still, I am awestruck to E.G.O’s potential whenever I see her berserk. </text>
  <text id="binah3_selection1">What E.G.O’s potential is, </text>
  <text id="binah3_selection2">Why I am awestruck,</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b1_1">You will never know these. You have never wielded it.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b2_1">Extracting E.G.O is one of my many works. That’s why I am naturally drawn to it.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b9">In fact, there are many weapons that hold enormous power in this world, besides E.G.O.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b10">Artifacts from outskirts, ruins, and singularities of the Wings, or crude inventions made in backstreets. Using them correctly would result in weapons that would fairly stand against abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b11">But giving those weapons to employees, who have never learnt about combat outside the basic training, is as futile as teaching a baby bird how to hunt.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b11_1">The Rabbits are specialized at killing. As long as they have enough ammunition, they can kill anything.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b11_2">Unlike our employees who can’t even handle weapons properly.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b12">Combat prowess is not one of the requirements, after all.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b13">But, they don’t have to learn how to use E.G.O</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b14">Its power grows accordingly to the wielder’s heart. You know how to use them at the moment your hand touches them.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b15">However, even with this power, most of the employees barley stand chance against abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b16">I haven’t seen anyone who can draw out its true potential, besides The Red Mist.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b17">Wielding E.G.O is donning someone else’s ego.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b18">It’s not the wielder’s power. It’s merely borrowed, imitated. </text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b19">If I knew that before I had been locked in here, I would have done anything to get my hands on them.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b20">Then the circumstances may be different greatly.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b21">After I am contained here, I am ordered to merely extract E.G.O, forbidden from holding it.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b22">They’re scared even though my bloodthirstiness is locked behind this metal wall.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b23">Do not worry. I have nothing left.</text>
  <text id="binah3_intro_b24">But you never know. The yearning for blood may rise again, for they are merely sealed, not eradicated.</text>

  <!-- 에피소드 4-->

  <text id="binah4_intro_b1">The world you stayed in was bright once.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b2">There were sun, moon, and clouds floating around them. It was the world of light.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b3">But you couldn’t stay there. They have robbed you of countless things.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b4">You lived with incomplete heart, holding onto the void.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b5">Nobody could understand you, nor embrace you.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b6">Eternal loss dominated your heart.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b7">I was one of your robbers. </text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b8">I was looking down on your struggles, standing on the top of the world.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b9">Not only you.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b10">I’ve seen many other struggles.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b11">It was no less futile than a bug’s wriggling. All I had to do was just step on them few times.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b12">But rarely, some of them clenched their teeth and climbed up, dragging their broken bodies.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b13">It looked like it will be a delightful trail. I sipped a cup of tea few times before I took off,</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b14">But as you can see, The Red Mist got the best of me.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b15">*Chuckles* and you gave me pain just as much as I gave you.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b16">You knew how to break one’s mind besides a gruesome torture or use of violence.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b17">After everything’s done, you collected every bit of human in me,</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b18">And threw them in this hole until even the soul is rotten.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b19">You may have told yourself that I deserve even more than this.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b20">Then you must be an upholder of justice, are you not?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b21">If it is so, why are you standing there looking like a prisoner just like me?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b22">You, who fearfully avoided my dying gaze.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b23">Why here, being punished like me?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b24">Well, while this is a satisfying view to me,</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b25">Is this what her great idealism came to be?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b26">You have dragged down your own hero.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b27">Do you think your duty is fulfilled after shedding a tear at the funeral of the innocents?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b28">When their bodies are still restless?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b29">Ironically, you found a hope in all this misery.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b30">The material that the Bucket is made of,</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b31">The gateway to everyone’s river.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b32">You used the Bucket to draw the water from other’s well.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b33">The Bucket rises with the water of a person from the well of a person.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b34">The ancient river, flowing at the bottom, even before the world is born.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b35">It’s drawn, whether the person consent or not.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b36">A change comes when the bucket that holds her saturated ideal and other’s ego.</text>
  <text id="binah4_selection1">About the Bucket.</text>
  <text id="binah4_selection2">About the change.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b37">Perhaps it’s hard to understand by just listening.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b38">How about I show you her miracles?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b39">It’s burdensome, but for you, anything.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b40">People who are selected long ago are waiting.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b41">I bring them accordingly to the record.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b42">Let me introduce. This is Nameless.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b43">He has nothing left, for he has abandoned everything that is himself long ago.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b44">To him, things like remains of the past or pain of the present are not important..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b45">He only sees future.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b46">Have you dreamt well?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e1">……..............</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b47">Yes, you shall dream eternally as you want.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b48">Employees will inject Cogito soon.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b49">What river does flow in you? What world do you hold in you?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b50">There are as many worlds as many people are. Discovering them is quite fun.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e2">………..………..………..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e3">………..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e4">………..Grr….grrrrrrrrrrr…..ggggggggg……</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b51">Nobody can see this…</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b52">That’s why they are adjusting the level of Cogito to my order, being blind and deaf. </text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b53">…………………</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b54">…………………………….. </text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b55">People should not make an eye contact with the drawer.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b56">But I must gaze into his eyes until the end. I can’t look away no matter how painful it is.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b57">In those eyes are unbearable void and things that should not exist that only I can endure.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b58">This is the punishment you gave me. </text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b59">Normal person would have gone mad thousands of times.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b60">Thanks to you, I can’t be granted with the bless of madness. The only thing I can do is to lock myself in my eyes…</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_e5">Gggggrrr……..</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b61">Now we wait.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b62">We need more time</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b63">To see if it can be sent up to start anew, or is to spend the eternity here in this pillar with me.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b64">Now, do you know what these pillars hold?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b65">Let’s say you’re lucky today.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b66">Sometimes, when Cogito level is inadequately adjusted, things that should not exist come up like fragments.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b67">Funny that I say this, but it’s like an adverse reaction that comes as a price for doing unspeakable to a human being.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b68">The Bucket draws other things than what we need, such as abyss that’s asleep beneath the humanity, subconsciousness, and every possibility.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b69">The things from the past, present, even the future. Everything.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b70">They’re out of our control. We can’t do anything about them.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b71">They float around, echoing with the abnormalities and eventually manifest themselves once the time comes. </text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b72">They’re what you call Ordeals.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b73">Fortunately, our firepower can suppress them, but that’s all we can do.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b74">Yes, as you heard, extracting an abnormality is my work,</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b75">But creating it was Carmen’s, who you buried long time ago.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b76">She’s the mother to all abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b77">How do you feel now that you know those abnormalities you faced are part of these pillars?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b78">You don’t feel anything to this agonizing view, do you?</text>
  <text id="binah4_intro_b79">Running away from your memory and acting like as if nothing has happened is your specialty, after all.</text>

    <!-- 에피소드 5-->
    <text id="binah5_intro_A1">You told me to sacrifice everything.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A2">Would you have done the same, if you knew this view?</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A3">I always wondered.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b1">This is no man’s land. The place of silence.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b2">Employees who visit here usually lose their mind and embrace the oblivion.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b3">It’s been a long time to have a talk with someone.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b4">You may be mistaken that I am the only being here.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b5">But I am countless companions who have been spending eternity with me.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b6">I’ll introduce you to one of them.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b7">You created the Bucket by rebuilding, dividing, proliferating Carmen’s body.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b8">You also created Cogito, the fluid of life and death.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b9">Only a very small dose existed back then. But it soon infinitely grew, and is now stagnated like a pond.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b10">Can you see?</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b11">She’s looking at us under the pond.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b12">I look at the bottom of it when it becomes too burdening. </text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b13">It feels like we are alone in the world when I do that.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b14">Sometimes, it feels like she is talking to me.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b15">I know, she is only an amalgamation of flesh, brain, and tentacles, floating beneath the pond.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b16">Some injected it, some went mad seeing her.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b17">Some gave their body and became lifeless and deathless. The others, who couldn’t take all of this, told everything to the head.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b18">This is collaboration of despair that you and she made.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b19">You’re still not qualified to look down into the pond.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b20">You need to look straight to your road to do so.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b21">Are you seeking redemption?</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b22">Or are you seeking to redeem everyone who are trapped here with me?</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b23">Whatever your goal is, you may think that saving this facility from sin is all you have to do.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b24">Even you, who haven’t get out of this facility for a long time,</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b25">would know that there are people hopelessly being killed by abnormalities.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b26">Every wing has their own share of painful stories.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b27">Nest, Backstreet, Ruins, Outskirts…  </text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b28">The unimaginable pain is prevailing in this world.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b29">I have seen everything, because I wasn’t being obsessed with unreachable ideal like you were.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b30">The world that you looked up and the world I looked down are different.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b31">You captured me and tortured me to your heart’s content, but we are still writhing in despair. </text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b32">Someone replaces me and becomes the arbiter of the Head and swing Claws at you.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b33">Even if you cut this cycle, it will be pointless.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b34">Broken wings will spread anew,</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b35">A brief resistance will soon be forgotten, and people will live on just because they can’t die.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b36">You may think that you have drawn me down.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b37">But I am still looking down on you twitching like bugs.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b38">I want to see you suffer in pain after realizing that this cycle will never end.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b39">I want to see you kneeling before the might of destiny. </text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b40">Despair, submit to your fate.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b41">Resist to your very end and finally break.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b42">Let the final resistance melt,</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_b43">and quietly flow through the water underneath the earth.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A4">She was badly wounded by Kali, yet she was our only way out.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A5">It was a miracle that we captured her. We were too far down the road filled with remorse to feel any guilty.</text>
    <text id="binah5_selection1">Dig through the head.</text>
    <text id="binah5_selection2">Dig through the head.</text>
    <text id="binah5_selection3">Dig through the head.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A6">How to avoid the head’s gaze, the way to get into one of the wings, and the way for us, the few, to survive.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A7">It was impossible to discover these on our own.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A8">She was barely breathing but her brain was still active. That was all we need.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A9">We dig through her head like we did to Carmen. We search for the way out.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A10">After that, we arduously collect those bits that are deformed.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A11">The guard at the gate of hell must always despair.</text>
    <text id="binah5_intro_A12">For him not to fall into the hell.</text>

    <!-- 에피소드 6-->
    <text id="binah6_intro_b1">This place has become barren now, after all.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_e1">P, please. Let me go. I did what you told me.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b2">Don’t you feel anything that the place you belonged to is now all ashes and rust?</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b3">Don’t be a buzzkill. Tell me how you feel..</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b4">I couldn’t feel anything looking at a meteor shower or shiny sunlight since my childhood,</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b5">But this, this makes me feel something.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b6">But it’s not enough.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b7">I’m still thirsty. </text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_e2">P, please. Please let me just go. You’ve got everything you want…</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b8">Why are you trembling? Where’s your guts? I can’t believe you tried to betray your comrades..</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b9">It wasn’t a perfect plan, but was an okay one.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b10">Thanks for those who trusted you, we have this beautiful view. </text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b11">I like killing people with that weapon, you know. That thing called trust.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b12">Scavengers will arrive soon.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b13">They are never late. .</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_e3">N, no! Please!.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b14">We have symbiotic relationship. I’m too busy to get rid of all the dregs. I leave those to them.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_e4">Not the scavengers, please!</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b15">Yes, that face.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b16">That’s what makes you look alive.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b17">…..</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b18">Ah, silence and metallic scent of tea, my best friends.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b19">You like them too, don’t you?</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b20">Now, to the next place.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b21">I don’t like following information given by some orange-haired kid…</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b22">But the weak ones give valuable information.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b23">What face will show me that they’re alive next?</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b24">Only trembling, dying things excite me.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b25">Only the sound of dying breath, and the face that cling onto fading life satisfy me.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b26">You and I are the same.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b27">We are the mutants of this age.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b28">No, let’s say that we are the ones that fit to this world.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b29">You planned everything.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b30">But whatever you do here, the world won’t change.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b31">Rising wings, syndicates from backstreets, things from outskirts, abyss from ruins, arbiters like me, claw, and eyes… you will never stand a chance against them alone.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b32">…But the world won’t change just by standing here, either.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b33">I will see everything you do. I will not avoid. I will not hide. I will not rest.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b34">I will never close my eyes, or turn my head.</text>
    <text id="binah6_intro_b35">Just go ahead like you have always been doing. Then you might make it. </text>

</localize>
