<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<localize>
	<text id="Manual_MainCategory_0">Basic Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_MainCategory_1">Management Preparation</text>
	<text id="Manual_MainCategory_2">Management Process</text>
	<text id="Manual_MainCategory_3">Emergency Situation</text>
	<text id="Manual_MainCategory_4">Finishing Manegement</text>
  
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_0">1. Your Goal</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_1">2. Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_2">3. Works</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_3">4. Abnormalities</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_4">5. Attack Types</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_5">6. E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_6">1. Deployment Part UI </text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_7">2. Hiring and Upgrading</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_8">3. Equipping E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_9">4. Deplyoing Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_10">1. Management Part UI </text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_11">2. Basic Control</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_12">3. Employee Control</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_13">4. Ordering a Work</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_14">5. Containment Unit UI </text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_15">6. Works</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_16">7. Qliphoth Counter</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_17">8. Work Penalty</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_18">10. Abnormality Observation</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_19">11. Tool-type Abnormality </text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_20">1. Emergency Situation</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_21">2. Emergency Alert Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_22">3. Suppressing an Abnormality </text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_23">4. Bullet</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_24">1. End of DAY</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_25">2. Memory Repository</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_26">3. Abnormality Selection</text>
	<text id="Manual_SubCategory_27">4. Unlocking Part</text>
  <text id="Manual_SubCategory_28">9. Department Functions</text>
  
	<text id="Manual_Node_0">What is an employee?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_1">Level and Promotion</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_2">What is an Abnormality?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_3">Risk Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_4">Right Panel</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_5">Department information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_6">Hiring Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_7">Checking and Upgrading Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_8">Activate E.G.O List</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_9">E.G.O Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_10">E.G.O Weapon</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_11">E.G.O Suit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_12">E.G.O Equipment Method</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_13">Checking Employee Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_14">Moving Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_15">Summoning Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_16">Ordering a Work UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_17">Click Order</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_18">Drag Right-Click Order</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_19">Phase of Works</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_20">Entering the Containment Unit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_21">Progressing the Work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_22">Completing the Work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_23">Qliphoth Counter</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_24">Qliphoth Meltdown</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_25">Ordeal</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_26">Qliphoth Overload</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_27">Open Encyclopedia</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_28">Observing</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_29">Production and Acquisition of E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_30">What is a Tool-type Abnormality?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_31">How to Use</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_32">How to Observe</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_33">Escape of Abnormality </text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_34">Death of Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_35">Suppression Order UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_36">Click Order</text>
	<text id="Manual_Node_37">Drag Right-Click Order</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_38">Abnormality Encyclopedia</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_39">Reminders when moving employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_40">Office Worker effect</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_41">Department long-service effect</text>
  <text id="Manual_Node_42">Panic of Employees</text>
  
	<text id="Manual_Text_0">Game Goal Description</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_1">1. You are the manager of Lobotomy Corporation.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_2">2. Your job is to safely manage the abnormalities and produce energy called 'Enkephalin' as the result.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_3">3. You are given a certain amount of energy you have to produce every day in order to proceed to the next DAY.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_4">What is an employee?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_5">Employees conduct 'works' to manage employees. They're your hands, so to say.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_6">Employee Values</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_7">Fortitude</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_8">As the HP of the employee increases, the value of Fortitude increases. You can increase employee's HP by conducting instinct work.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_9">HP (Health Point): Physical strength of the employee. An employee whose HP drops to 0 will die.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_10">Prudence</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_11">As the SP of the employee increases, the value of Prudence increases. You can increase employee's SP by conducting insight work.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_12">SP (Sanity Point): Mental strength of employees. An employee whose SP drops to 0 will panic.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_13">Temperance</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_14">Temperance increases as an employee's Work Speed and Success Rate increases. You can increase employee's Work speed and Success rate by conducting attachment work.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_15">Work Speed: Employees with higher Work Speed complete works faster.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_16">Success rate: Employees with high Success Rate will produce more Enkephalin and take less damage when working.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_17">Justice</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_18">Justice incrases as an employee's Attack Speed and Movement Speed increases. You can increase employee's Attack Speed and Movement Speed by conducting repression work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_19">Attack Speed: Employees with higher Attack Speed attacks faster.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_20">Movement Speed: Employees with higher Movement Speed travels faster to their destination.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_21">Level and Promotion</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_22">Employee Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_23">Employees can be promoted from level 1 to level 5. Higher level means that the employee is more talented.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_24">Values also have level that ranges from 1 to 5.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_25">Employee Promotion</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_26">When employees have a certain amount of status experience, the level of the value related to the status increases.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_27">The higher value level allows employees to conduct a work of higher level.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_28">Employee's level is based on the sum of their value levels. Employees' level will increase as thier value level does.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_29">Work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_30">There are four types of work that can be conducted on abnormalities. Among the four types of work, you have to find the most appropriate work for each abnormality and steadily proceed to produce energy.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_31">Instinct</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_32">The work that satisfies the physiological needs of an abnormality. It requires employees to directly contact the abnormalities. Because of that, only employees with high Fortitude can conduct high level instinct work. Employees who conduct instinct work will benefit from increased HP, which is related to Fortitude.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_33">Insight</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_34">The work that improves the overall environment which the abnormality is currently in. As each Abnormality has different requirement regarding their environment, only employees with high Prudence can conduct high level insight work. Employees who conduct Insight work will benefit from increased SP, which is related to Prudence.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_35">Attachment</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_36">The work that satisfies the social desires of Abnormality. As only limited interaction is allowed, only employees with high Temperance level can conduct high level attachment work. Employees who conduct attachment work will benefit from increased Work Speed and Success Rate, which are related to Temperance.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_37">Repression</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_38">The work that suppress the existential entity and spiritual desire of the abnormality. As this work requires a delicate adjustment of intensity based on clear and fair evaluation, only employees with high Justice level can conduct high level repression work. Employees who conduct repression work will benefit from increased Attack Speed and Movement Speed, which are related to Justice.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_39">What is an Abnormality?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_40">Abnormalities are entities that are originated from humanity's sub-conciousness. We can extract Enkephalin from them through appropriate management.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_41">Risk Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_42">However, abnormalities are never safe.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_43">Please refer to the risk level below when managing abnormalities</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_44">Containment Unit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_45">Encyclopedia</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_46">Abnormalities with the lowest aggressiveness. It usually does not do much harm, and depending on the situation, it can have a positive impact on employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_47">This class of abnormality can cause a variety of damage to employees. However, if you manage them well, they will not cause a serious problem.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_48">Abnormalities that requires more than twice as much attention of ZAYIN, TETH abnormalities. They can easily kill a handful of employees, but a good manager will not let that happen. </text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_49">Abnormalities that are very dangerous and destructive. They are hostile to the vast majority of employees and can result in dozens of casualties when they escape.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_50">The most dangerous abnormalities are labeled with this class. You must always give attention to these abnormalities. It is a relief if these abnormalities escape, and are suppresed before they destroy the whole department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_51">Attack Type</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_52">Abnormalities have four types of attacks.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_53">RED</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_54">The type of attack that causes physical damage. When attacked by the RED type, the HP of the employee will be reduced</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_55">WHITE</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_56">The type of attack that causes mental damage. When attacked by the WHITE type, the SP of the employee will be reduced.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_57">BLACK</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_58">A compound of physical damage and mental damage. When attacked by the BLACK type, the HP and SP of the employee will be reduced.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_59">PALE</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_60">It is the death itself. Strong body and great mind are all equal before the death. PALE type attack will cause damage in proportion to the total HP of the employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_61">E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_62">E.G.O (Extermination of Geometrical Organ) is an equipment made to fight the abnormalities.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_63">There are E.G.O Weapon (Attack equipment) and E.G.O Suit (Defense equipment).</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_64">E.G.O can be extracted from abnormalities that have been managed and observed to the certain level.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_65">As these equipment are basically processed essence of abnormalities, they can defend or attack in R,W,B,P types just like abnormalities.  </text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_66">There are total of five levels in E.G.O. E.G.O with higher level will have higher attack power and defense power against certain attack types.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_67">ATK - DEF Mechanism</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_68">E.G.O with high level will benefit from increased attack and defense against abnormalities with lower level.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_69">Conversely, E.G.O with low level will suffer from decreased attack and defense against abnormalities with higher level.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_70">Deploy Part UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_71">Right panel</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_72">Checking Highest level of Ordeal</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_73">You can see the highest level of the Ordeal on this day</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_74">Ordeal appears as work progresses.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_75">LOB</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_76">LOB is point you can get as you manage through the game.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_77">It is used when hiring and upgrading employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_78">E.G.O list Button</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_79">This button activates the list of E.G.O.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_80">Hire Button</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_81">This button is used for hiring employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_82">Department Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_83">Mission</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_84">It shows the missions you can progress on this day.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_85">If you clear a mission, you can conduct researches that are assigned to each department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_86">Contained Abnormalities</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_87">It shows the information of the abnormalities placed in this department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_88">The Abnormality that has not been observed is labeled as '?'.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_89">Department Description</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_90">It shows the description of this department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_91">Research</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_92">It shows the research this department has.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_93">Researches can be very helpful for managing abnormalities.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_94">Hiring Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_95">You can hire employees by pressing the Hire button.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_96">You can hire employees of the default level by pressing the Hire button again.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_97">Employees at default level require 1 LOB to hire.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_98">Changing Value Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_99">You can raise the level of desired value by clicking on the arrows.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_100">Additional LOB is required when raising value levels.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_101">Higher value level requires more LOB points</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_102">Changing Appearance</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_103">You can spend LOB to change the appearance of employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_104">Checking and Upgrading Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_105">Already hired employees can be upgraded using LOB.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_106">You can click on a hired employee to check the information of that employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_107">You can upgrade them in the same way you did when hiring.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_108">Activate E.G.O List</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_109">You can activate the E.G.O list by pressing E.G.O List button.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_110">E.G.O Weapon</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_111">It is an equipment that changes the attack damage of an employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_112">Attack Type</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_113">E.G.O's Attack Type.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_114">Damage</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_115">E.G.O's Attack Damage</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_116">Speed</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_117">E.G.O Attack Speed</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_118">Attack Range</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_119">E.G.O's Attack Range</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_120">E.G.O Suit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_121">It is equipment that changes the defensive .</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_122">E.G.O's defense factor against each attack type</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_123">If defense factor is lower than 1.0, that means that E.G.O is strong against that attack type.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_124">If defense factor is higher than 1.0, that means that E.G.O is more vulnerable against that attack type.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_125">E.G.O Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_126">Sorting E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_127">You can selectively view only E.G.O of a certain level by clicking on the tab.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_128">Detail</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_129">It shows the details and special abilities of E.G.O.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_130">Requirements</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_131">Some E.G.O may require a certain value level and employee level.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_132">E.G.O Gift</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_133">E.G.O which may be acquired at the completion of work. It affects the status of employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_134">How to Equip E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_135">Select the floor.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_136">Select the employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_137">Select the empty E.G.O slot. E.G.O will not be equipped if the employee does not meet the requirements of the E.G.O.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_138">Check E.G.O that the employee has equipped.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_139">How to deploy employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_140">Click an employee</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_141">Drag and drop an employee into the department in which you want to place them.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_142">Management Part UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_143">Target amount of PE-Box</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_144">You must gather a certain amount of PE-Box to finish the DAY. The gauge fills each time a PE-BOX is produced after the work on an abnormality is completed.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_145">Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_146">A gauge that predicts the Qliphoth Meltdown. Each time an employee enters the containment unit, the gauge increases by 1. If the gauge is filled to the end, Qliphoth Meltdown or Ordeals will be triggered.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_147">Mission List</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_148">This is a list of missions that can be done on this DAY.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_149">Adjusting Speed</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_150">These buttons can be used to control the speed of the game.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_151">Work Log</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_152">It shows the history of the work that has been done so far, casualties, and panic status.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_153">Recovery Gauge</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_154">Whenever the recovery gauge hits the end, the HP and SP of the employees in the center of each department are restored. However, the recovery gauge will stop working if an abnormality enters the center of the department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_155">Basic Control</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_156">Camera Control</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_157">Right click and drag to the direction you want</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_158">You can move up, down, left, and right by pressing 'W, A, S, D'.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_159">You can zoom in and out of the screen by rolling the mouse wheel.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_160">Time Control</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_161">Time Deceleration: Q</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_162">Time Acceleration: E</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_163">Pause: SPACE</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_164">You can order employees even when the game is paused.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_165">Confirm employee information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_166">You can see the information of the employee by hovering your mouse over them. If you click an employee, the information UI for that employee will be fixed on the screen.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_167">Moving Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_168">Click an employee you want to move. When moving more than two employees, left-click and drag to select employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_169">With an employee selected, right-click the place where you want to move the employee to.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_170">Summoning Employees</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_171">Return employees who have moved to other departments back to their department. (Control team research required)</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_172">Work Order UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_173">Risk level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_174">The maximum number of PE-Boxes that can be produced by working on this abnormality. </text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_175">Different work results by the number of PE-Box</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_176">Attack type and damage during work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_177">Change Department (Employees will be able to work in other departments once the related Control Team research is completed.)</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_178">Employee Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_179">The chance of successing a work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_180">The time it takes for this employee's work to finish.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_181">Click Order</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_182">1. Left click on a containment unit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_183">2. Select a work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_184">3. Select an employee</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_185">Drag Right Click Order</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_186">1. Click or drag an employee</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_187">2. Right click on containment unit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_188">3. Select a work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_189">4. Select a Employee</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_190">Containment unit UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_191">Risk level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_192">Qliphoth Counter</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_193">Number of unique PE-Boxes</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_194">Number of PE-Boxes produced in previous work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_195">Steps of a work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_196">Each time employees work, abnormalities will produce PE-Box (Positive Enkephalin BOX) or NE-Box (Negative Enkephalin BOX). Only PE-Box can be refined and processed into energy.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_197">The manager's goal is to find out how to safely produce as many as PE-Boxes from abnormalities.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_198">The mechanism of work is simple.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_199">Entering the Containment Unit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_200">Progressing the Work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_201">Completing the Work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_202">Entering the Containment Unit</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_203">When recieved an order, employees will move to their designated containment unit.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_204">Each time an employee enters the containment unit, the Qliphoth meltdown gauge increases by 1. If you wish to know more, refer to the Qliphoth Meltdown article.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_205">Please be aware that some abnormalities may attack immediately when an employee enters the containment unit if they do not comply with the management method.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_206">Fear Damage</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_207">If an employee encounters an abnormality, they may be mentall damaged.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_208">Abnormalities that has higher risk level than an employee will deal more mental damage to that employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_209">Mental damage also applies when an abnormality escapes and encounters an employee outside the containment unit.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_210">Work Progress</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_211">Success Rate</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_212">Each abnormality has a different success rate for each work. So, depending on what you do, the outcome of the work may change.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_213">The Success Rate is affected by the work level and the employee's Success Rate.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_214">Success Rate determines success and failure of a work.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_215">Success and Failure of work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_216">Work Successful</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_217">The abnormality will produce PE-Box.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_218">Work Failure</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_219">The abnormality will produce NE-Box.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_220">The abnormality that produced NE-Box will attack the employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_221">An employee whose HP or SP drop to 0 may die or panic.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_222">If an employee dies or panics during a work, the work will be terminated prematurely and remaining E-Boxes will be produced as NE-Box.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_223">Work Complete</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_224">The target PE-Box gauge fills as much as the produced PE-Box.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_225">The number of PE-Box produced will determine the result of the work. There are 3 types of reslut. Bad, Normal, and Good.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_226">The PE-Box will then stored as unique PE-Box of the corresponding abnormality. With unique PE-Box, you can proceed observation on that abnormality and produce E.G.O.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_227">Qliphoth Counter</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_228">Some Abnormality may cause a decrease in the Qliphoth Counter when you manage them in a wrong way or when work is finished.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_229">The Qliphoth counter can be found in the UI of the containment unit.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_230">When the Qliphoth counter reaches 0, the abnormality may escape from the containment unit or uses its special abilities.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_231">Be careful and try not to make Qliphoth Counter to reach 0.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_232">Work Penalty</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_233">Qliphoth Overload</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_234">WAW and ALEPH Abnormalities decrease the success rate as the number of works done on them increases.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_235">The containment unit where the Qliphoth Overload occurred shows the reduced success rate, and you can also check for overload in the Work Command UI.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_236">Containment units where Qliphoth Overload occured will return to normal when Qliphoth meltdown breaks out. When this happens, all of the reduced success rates will be restored to their original success rate.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_237">Qliphoth Meltdown</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_238">Meltdown Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_239">Every time the Qliphoth Meltdown is triggered, the level rises.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_240">Qliphoth Meltdown Gauge</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_241">Each time an employee enters the containment unit, the gauge increases by 1.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_242">When the gauge reaches the end, a Qliphoth Meltdown occurs throughout the facility.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_243">As the Meltdown Level rises, the number of containment units in which Qliphoth meltdown occurs increases.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_244">Meltdown Alarm and Occurrence</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_245">An alarm timer is shown on the containment unit where Qliphoth Meltdown occured. The timer will go down gradually.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_246">When the alarm timer reaches 0, the Qliphoth Counter of the abnormality in the corresponding containment unit becomes 0, and the PE-BOX will decrease.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_247">Countermeasures agianst Qliphoth Metldown</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_248">The Qliphoth Meltdown is lifted as soon as an employee enters the containment unit where the meltdown occurred.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_249">The Qliphoth meltdown gauge will not rise by doing so.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_250">However, the reduced success rate due to Qliphoth overload will still be reflected in the work.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_251">Ordeals</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_252">At a certain level of Qliphoth Meltdown, an Ordeal appears instead of meltdown.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_253">'Ordeal' is a kind of Abnormality that has not been refined. There are four risk levels for Ordeals: Dawn, Noon, Dusk, and Midnight. As the level of meltdown increases, the higher the level of Ordeal appears.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_254">Ordeal will hinder the management of abnormality in a variety of ways. However, because the Ordeals are also abnormalities, you can give orders to the employees to suppress the them. For the suppression of the Ordeal, see the 'Suppressing Abnormalities' section.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_255">Activating Encyclopedia</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_256">You can activate the encyclopedia window by clicking on the name of the abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_257">Abnormality Encyclopedia</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_258">Abnormality Story</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_259">It shows the story of the abnormality. The story is updated every observation level.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_260">Abnormality Information</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_261">Basic information about working on this abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_262">Abnormality Management Guide</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_263">Success rate of each work</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_264">Qliphoth Counter and the defense against attack types</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_265">E.G.O which can be produced and obtained at the current observation level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_266">Observation Progress</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_267">Using unique PE-Box</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_268">You can unlock information by spending unique PE-Box of each abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_269">Observation Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_270">When you unlock all information in one category, the observation level increases.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_271">Production and Acquisition of E.G.O</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_272">E.G.O Gift</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_273">An employee can get E.G.O Gift with a low chance when completing the work on an abnormality after achieving a certain observation level. E.G.O Gift affects employee status.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_274">E.G.O Production</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_275">Achieving the certain observation level will allow you to produce the E.G.O of that Abnormality. Production of E.G.O requires its unique PE-BOX.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_276">What is a Tool-type Abnormality?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_277">Unlike other abnormality, Tool-type abnormality is an abnormality that emphasizes 'how to use' rather than 'how to manage'.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_278">Types of Tool-type abnormality</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_279">1. Instantaneous type: Employees can use this type of Tool-type abnormality to gain immediate effect.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_280">2. Equipment type: The effect is obtained when the employee equips this type of Tool-type abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_281">3. Continuous Type: Employees must constantly use this type of Tool-type abnormality to gain its effect.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_282">On every fourth day (Day 4, Day 9...), a new Tool-type abnormality will be added.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_283">How to Use Tool-type abnormalities</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_284">1. Click on the abnormality of the Tool-type abnormality to order an employee to use it.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_285">2. An employee will use or equip the Tool-type abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_286">3. You can order employees to stop using or return them by clicking once again on the containment unit of Tool-type abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_287">How to Observe</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_288">The Tool-type abnormality's Encyclopedia is automatically updated according to the number and time of use.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_289">Escape of abnormality</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_290">If the Qliphoth counter reaches 0, the abnormality in the containment unit will escape.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_291">Also, if you violate management methods, abnormality may escape.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_292">Escaped abnormalities are to be suppressed quickly. If you wish to know more about suppression, refer to 'Suppressing Abnormalities'.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_293">Employee's Death and Panic</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_294">Employee's Death</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_295">Any employee whose HP dros 0 due to damage from an R, B, P attack will die.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_296">If an employee dies, all E.G.O that the employee has been equipped will be destroyed.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_297">Employee's Panic</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_298">Any employee whose SP drops 0 due to damage from a W, B attack will panic</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_299">A panicked employee can return to their original state when they have recovered as much as the full SP with W, B attack of E.G.O.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_300">If you end the DAY with panicked employees, they will be disposed of.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_301">Emergency Alert Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_302">If an abnormality escapes during management or employees are killed or panic, the alarm will sound depending on the severity.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_303">First Trumpet</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_304">It is a situation where an abnormality escapes and applies some minor harm to the facility and employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_305">Second Trumpet</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_306">It is not too late to improve the situation. If you are a competent manager, you will able to work without a problem until this level, except the sacrifice of some employees.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_307">Third Trumpet</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_308">It is a miracle to turn the table. The majority of employees is dead, and the escaped abnormalities can't be taken care of.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_309">Suppression Order UI</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_310">Risk Level</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_311">Attack Type</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_312">Defense Type</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_313">Defense Factor against attack types of the abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_314">You can use E.G.O that is the abnormality is weak to, (the defensive factor 1.0 or more) to suppress it more efficiently. </text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_315">Employee Status</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_316">You can check employees' current HP, SP, and E.G.O equipment status.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_317">Click Order</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_318">1. Click the escaped abnormality or the its containment unit.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_319">2. Select the employees. When a certain Control Team research is completed, you can order employees in other departments to suppress the abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_320">3. You can cancel the suppression order by clicking on the employee who's suppressing.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_321">Drag Right-Click Command</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_322">1. Click or drag to select the employees who will proceed suppression.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_323">2. With your employees selected, right-click on the escaped Abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_324">What is a bullet?</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_325">You can use the bullet by conducting research in the middle department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_326">The quantity of bullets is equal to the number of Qliphoth Meltdown gauges.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_327">Once used, the bullet will not reload until the Qliphoth Meltdown is occurred. When the Qliphoth Meltdown breaks out, the bullets will be fully reloaded by the number of default number.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_328">How to use a bullet</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_329">1. Click the bullet UI or press the number key corresponding to each bullet to activate the bullet.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_330">2. When the bullet is activated, the mouse cursor changes to the shape of the activated bullet.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_331">3. Point your mouse at the target and click the mouse to fire the bullet.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_332">4. Click the bullet UI again or press the numeric key again to disable the bullet.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_333">Ending the DAY.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_334">It shows what missions are cleared on this day.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_335">It shows increased status experiences and level of each employee.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_336">Every time you end your DAY, you will receive LOB as a reward depending on how well you did.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_337">The higher the employee's survival rate, the higher the rank and the more LOBs you can acquire.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_338">If you finish the DAY with an abnormality that has escaped, there is a penalty, which reduces reward LOB.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_339">Deciding to Proceed</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_340">After the DAY is finished, you can choose whether to move on to the next DAY or retry this DAY.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_341">If you choose to retry, both the deceased employee and the destroyed E.G.O from previous try will be recovered. However, please note that the observations and acquired E.G.O from previous try will be gone.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_342">Memory Repository</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_343">Memory Repository is updated every 5 day (DAY 1, DAY 6, DAY 11...).</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_344">Unlike retry, if you go back to the memory repository, your observations to date and E.G.O will be maintained. However, please note that abnormalities and the containment unit unlock progress will return to the state of the corresponding repository's day.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_345">You can choose to go back to Memory Repository in ESC Menu.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_346">Selecting Abnormalities</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_347">Each time you move on to the next DAY, you will have to choose one abnormality to manage.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_348">Carefully read the phrase of the abnormality and choose.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_349">Unlocking Part</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_350">When you move on to the next DAY, you need to choose the containment unit location for the new abnormality.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_351">Each time you unlock a containment unit, the department's unlock level increases.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_352">When the unlock level of the departments reaches the maximum, a new department can be unlocked.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_353">In case of a department opening at the same time, you can open the containment unit of another department without having to achieve the maximum unlock level of one department.</text>
	<text id="Manual_Text_354">The higher the risk level, the more dangerous and difficult to manage.</text>

  
  <!--Added at 2018.01.26-->
  <text id="Manual_Text_355">Department Function</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_356">It shows the department’s functions.</text>

  <text id="Manual_Text_357">Reminders When Moving Employees</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_358">If every employee is in a department that they don’t belong to, a countdown starts.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_359">If not a single employee comes back to their original department, every office worker in their department panics.</text>

  <text id="Manual_Text_360">Office Worker effects</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_361">Office worker effects applies accordingly to the survival rate of the office workers in the departments. The effects vary by a department.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_362">Effect level increases as unlock level of the department increases. Higher levels have better effects.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_363">Office Worker effect level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_364">Level 3: Office worker survival rate 100%~80%, Unlock level 5</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_365">Level 2: Office worker survival rate 80%~50%, Unlock level 3~4</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_366">Level 1: Office worker survival rate 50%~30%, Unlock level 1~2</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_367">If office workers die or panic during and the office worker survival rate is decreased as a result, effect level decreases.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_368">If office worker survival rate reaches zero, the effects are removed from the relevant department.</text>

  <text id="Manual_Text_369">Department long-service effect</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_370">An employee can gain long-service effect accordingly to their service time.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_371">Long-service effects vary by a department. An employee who gained long-service effects are gifted with the title and a special armband.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_372">However, if an employee that gained long-service effect is moved to another department, the effects will be removed.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_373">Long-service effect level</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_374">Level 1: 1~2 days</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_375">Level 2: 3~6 days</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_376">Level 3: 7 days or more</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_377">Additional effects and a special armband are gifted to the employee who worked the longest among the employees that worked 7 days or more.</text>
  
  <text id="Manual_Text_378">If all employees in a department die, the entire department's Success Rate decreases.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_379">If all employees die, office workers will commit suicide and the office survival effects of the departments will be eliminated.</text>

  <text id="Manual_Text_380">Employee Panic</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_381">3. The type of behavior of a panicked employee is determined by the employee's highest value.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_382">Fortitude ▶ Murder</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_383">Prudence ▶ Suicide </text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_384">Temperance ▶ Wandering</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_385">Justice ▶ Opening containment units</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_386">4. The higher level an employee has, more difficult to restore them back to normal status when they panic. Also, they can cause a serious damage to the facility.</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_387">5. If you finish a DAY with panicked employees present, be careful as they will be disposed of.</text>

  <text id="Manual_Text_388">Defender</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_389">Attacker</text>
  <text id="Manual_Text_390">(Risk Level)</text>

</localize>